Chapter 1711 - The Chance in the Iron Plate

Luck!

Those who understood the true reason for Steamed Bun’s actions would all think this way. After all, this wasn’t a prediction that had come from Glory experience or awareness, it was just a childish instinct. Steamed Bun probably didn’t understand the true danger of the attack that Wu Qi had Cruel Silence execute.

But this kind of childish instinct, was it a type of intuition? It was hard to say. In any case, what happened now was that Cruel Silence was stopped short by Steamed Bun’s Paralysis Needle, and after that, well, Tang Rou had never stopped Soft Mist’s attacks. When Cruel Silence suddenly appeared right in front of her, his dagger just about to hit her, Tang Rou had been extremely startled. In this kind of crucial moment, she had acted without thinking. Her attacks immediately focused on Cruel Silence.

Without Steamed Bun’s interference, Tang Rou’s instinctive reaction really might not have come fast enough. But now, with Steamed Bun disrupting things, Tang Rou’s immediate change of target became a huge burst!

If she hadn’t burst forth with an attack, then she would have been hit. In this kind of dangerous moment, did Tang Rou’s ferocity even need to be mentioned?

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had come over to help. But he didn’t go to attack Cruel Silence; instead, he headed toward Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf, blocking Sun Xiang’s close-range support.

Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer and Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain were in a similar situation. Because these two characters were standing at a long-range, no one was coming to disrupt them. Zhou Zekai readjusted his aim to try and force back Happy’s surging counterattack.

At this moment, Jiang Botao was truly a bit speechless.

He still remembered that not long ago, he had been the focus of Happy’s fire. How come, in the blink of an eye, his Empty Waves was left hanging out to dry? Happy’s four characters, he couldn’t see the face of a single one. What were they doing? Was there still a clear strategic goal? Was there still a firm plan?

It was a mess, completely a mess.

Right now, this was just a mess of a battle. Happy didn’t have a clear goal or intent, they were just chaotically fighting. Samsara could only deal with the attacks as they came. With Happy’s strange rhythm, Samsara had actually been forced on the defensive.

This can’t continue!

Left to the side, Jiang Botao had a clear view of the battle. Happy didn’t seem to have any organization, nor any strategy, but they definitely still had a goal. This kind of large chaotic battle was a frequent sight in Glory’s in-game Arena. It was a path for the unskilled. Happy’s skill was of course much higher than that of in-game players, but they couldn’t change how low-end this kind of chaotic fight was.

But this was exactly Happy’s goal. They wanted to drag Samsara down into this low-level rhythm and atmosphere, and then use their thorough low-level experience to defeat Samsara. Right now, they could already see the effects. Samsara was being forced on the defensive, because this didn’t follow the match logic that they were used to. The pro players on the field right now were used to taking a step and looking three steps ahead. But now, they couldn’t see three steps ahead, Happy took one step and they followed one step, and then, that was all…

They had to control the rhythm. They couldn’t be dragged along by Happy.

Jiang Botao was very conscious of this, and the other three from Samsara had noticed this as well. But Happy was pressing hard on Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf and Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence, so for now the two of them could only follow Happy’s rhythm. On the other hand, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer was far away, and no one was interfering with his adjustments.

No longer protecting those two people. No longer trying to disrupt Happy’s offensive. Cloud Piercer’s attack suddenly had a clear direction.

Lord Grim!

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim.

Well done.

Jiang Botao praised him internally. Zhou Zekai’s judgment was as fast and accurate as ever. Focusing Lord Grim was the best way of breaking the current situation. There was in fact some order hidden in the chaos of Happy’s fighting, and Ye Xiu was the only one taking responsibility for it. It was his Lord Grim that used the fast rhythm of switching between low-level skills in order to connect everyone else.

Attack Lord Grim, and Happy’s chaotic fighting would truly be reduced to nothing but a low-level struggle, and Sun Xiang and Wu Qi would be able to find a breakthrough point.

One after the other, Zhou Zekai and Jiang Botao began a pincer attack. The two didn’t communicate in their team channel, but the coordination of their offense demonstrated a tacit understanding beyond compare. Even though Zhou Zekai and Sun Xiang were the Best Partners of this season, but Jiang Botao, who had tied together Zhou Zekai and the rest of Samsara when he joined the team, was unquestionably the player that understood Zhou Zekai the best. It was only because he wasn’t as flashy onstage as Zhou Zekai or Sun Xiang was; his coordination, his understanding, it was always demonstrated quietly.

Right now, for example, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer began firing powerful shots toward Lord Grim. In comparison, Jiang Botao seemed less hurried, Empty Waves’ movements seemed to be slower by half a beat, but this half-beat difference perfectly cut off Lord Grim’s path of retreat.

The one who would shine beautifully on the battlefield would be Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer. And amidst this beauty, Jiang Botao would be doing the tiring, dirty work. He quietly supported Zhou Zekai. This was what he had always done after arriving at Samsara.

Dodge!

Under Cloud Piercer’s offensive, Ye Xiu had no choice but to control Lord Grim to dodge.

But to the right was Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion. If he dodged in that direction, the fire would interrupt the rhythm of those two. If he dodged back, Empty Waves’ Wave Slash had already caught up, he had no way of stepping back and adjusting. Right now, it seemed he had only one choice, going left…

Going left, he would leave the three-person offensive unit he’d established; going left, he would be acting within Samsara’s predictions, and there would definitely be a more difficult offensive waiting for him.

But aside from this, did he have any other choice?

Go forward?

Today, Happy had already demonstrated their courage numerous times. Under this kind of pressure, they frequently surged forward to fight fire with fire, even using their healer as an additional source of raw power. When they remembered Lord Grim swiftly charging forward, dodging the bullets that flew his way, with his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella shifting hundreds and thousands of times in his hands, countless people were already jumping with excitement. But this time, Ye Xiu let them down.

Lord Grim didn’t charge forward to Cloud Piercer, but nor did he move to the left as Samsara was hoping.

He stepped back!

Jiang Botao was stunned.

Ye Xiu hadn’t chosen to meet Cloud Piercer and his gunfire head on. He’d instead chosen to retreat backward, he was running toward the area under Empty Waves’ control.

A huge surprise!

Everyone had been mentally prepared for him to charge through Cloud Piercer’s fire, but retreating backward, breaking through Empty Waves’ end, no one had expected this.

Because Jiang Botao’s movement was slow by half a beat.

This seemed as though his reaction was delayed compared to Zhou Zekai, but this was his strength. Acting just a hair slower meant that his movement was more effective. He waited to see Zhou Zekai’s offensive before confirming how he would coordinate with him. With no attitude of fighting for the spotlight, his actions seemed simpler, yet they were more useful.

It could be said like this.

Although Cloud Piercer’s fire was sharp, Empty Waves’ coordination was more dangerous.

But there was a prerequisite, this danger depended on Cloud Piercer’s powerful offensive. Without the pressure of this offensive, this so-called danger no longer existed.

Jiang Botao’s style was completely different from Wu Qi’s. He wasn’t trying hide the deadly amidst the beauty. He simply used a more pragmatic style to support the beautiful offense of his teammates, especially that of Zhou Zekai.

And his kind of pragmatism was more solid and reliable, so much so that although people would think of charging Zhou Zekai’s spearhead, no one thought of charging Jiang Botao’s iron plate. But Ye Xiu did exactly that.

“What’s this guy trying to do?”

The pro players all let out exclamations of surprise. Everyone understood Jiang Botao’s style and his way of cooperating with Zhou Zekai. They all knew that under these circumstances, Jiang Botao’s area would pose a greater threat.

But after everyone expressed their surprise, they all couldn’t help but exchange glances.

“Reverse thinking?” Yu Wenzhou said.

“That’s bold,” Huang Shaotian said. As Glory’s most famous opportunist, he could understand Ye Xiu’s thought of “this isn’t an opportunity, but I’ll make it one.” But this didn’t necessarily mean that this was a beautiful choice, only that it was an extremely bold one.

No one would think that this was an opportunity, no one would make this kind of choice. As time went on, even Jiang Botao himself had gotten used to this kind of situation. He hadn’t slacked off because of this, but when Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim charged at him, he discovered that he was extremely unfamiliar with dealing with this kind of situation. He discovered that, in reality, he didn’t have much experience in facing this kind of powerful charge. Most of the time, the opponent would be scared into retreating, and those that charged forward didn’t do so with courage and belief, they had simply had a lapse of judgment and made the mistake of crashing against the iron plate.

Ye Xiu hadn’t made a mistake, Ye Xiu had acted on purpose. What he demonstrated was still that one word: fast.

Turning around while retreating, beginning a skill while turning, moving at a high speed while beginning the skill.

Jiang Botao saw all of this, but he couldn’t keep up with this kind of rhythm. His awareness, his control, it all seemed to have entered cooldown. His controls hadn’t stopped, but he himself knew, slow, too slow, compared to Ye Xiu’s fast, he was far too slow.

In the blink of an eye, Lord Grim had arrived before him. That Wave Wheel Slasher that had been viewed as an iron plate was now fluttering like a tissue in the wind. Cloud Piercer’s bullets were still chasing Lord Grim, but at this moment, in a trance, Jiang Botao almost felt like those bullets were coming at him, that they were covering Lord Grim’s offensive.

Colliding Stab!

Lord Grim crashed into Empty Waves. Right after, Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, those two characters also switched their target immediately, suddenly rushing in this direction as well. Su Mucheng’s heavy firepower on the other end of the map had already begun blasting toward Empty Waves.

Switch… switching targets again?

Happy’s rhythm had truly made Jiang Botao dizzy. There was no organization sometimes, yet in just a moment, this kind focused fire could burst forth. This rapid switching meant that Samsara was always chasing Happy’s rhythm. They’d firmly lost the initiative!

Chapter 1712 - Fight Two Together

Had Happy already established the upper hand?

It was clear that Happy had the initiative on the field right now, causing many people to think this way. But while the situation on the battlefield was always fluctuating, the overall advantage could be seen from the data.

Health!

After such a long battle, the health of all eight of the characters still on the battlefield had been depleted. Especially since there were no healers left, comparing this stat became extremely clear.

Before this, in terms of total health, Happy was lagging behind. In the two exchanges earlier, Happy had been catching up under unfavorable situations. In order to catch up and complete their own attacks, they had no choice but to suffer some additional damage that may have been otherwise avoidable.

But after these two exchanges, Happy grasped the rhythm, and they had focused Jiang Botao's Empty Waves twice already.

Focusing fire was the main way of killing an opponent during a team battle, but when to focus, when not to focus, when to stop focusing, there was much to learn. Even if five players controlled their characters to fire all of their attacks toward one target, that didn't guarantee that this was a successfully threatening focus. If focused attacks weren't timed at a good opportunity, they might not even be able to successfully focus the target in the first place.

Right now, Happy had seized a good opportunity to focus. Lord Grim and Dancing Rain's attacks were already on display, and Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion were close behind. Then now, how long this focus could last, when to stop focusing, these were the important questions. If they simply outputted damage without any thought, then they might discover that after dealing an amount of damage that they were satisfied with, the damage they suffered might be even greater than what they'd dealt.

But right now, Samsara didn't even want to give this question to Happy. They hoped to stop their focusing offensive before Soft Mist and Steamed Bun began attacking. Even though they had the upper hand when it came to overall health, Jiang Botao's Empty Waves had the lowest health remaining out of all eight characters still on the battlefield. He was the only one who had fallen below 50%. If Happy actually succeeded with this focus, and Samsara wasn't fast enough in disrupting them, he might actually die to this offensive wave.

Even if they saved him in the end, they had no healer. A character with extremely low health would be a great burden. In the team competition, 50% damage split between five characters, versus 50% damage taken by one character, those were two entirely different situations. The advantage would shift drastically.

Shadow Clone Technique!

With this kind of "I'd rather take damage as well than let Jiang Botao suffer alone" attitude, Wu Qi directly used his fastest movement skill. With a Shadow Clone Technique, Cruel Silence directly threw himself into the center of Happy's offensive.

This position was even more convenient for Happy to target than Empty Waves' current position. He was right at the center of Lord Grim, Soft Mist, and Steamed Bun Invasion's lines of attack.

Switch targets?

Then this focus fire would be split, and Empty Waves and Cruel Silence would take it together.

Don't switch targets?

The position that Cruel Silence had taken now was an obstacle to Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion's offensives as well.

A choice dangled in front of Happy, sugar hiding poison.

Lord Grim attacked.

Did they switch?

Wu Qi was prepared. Of these two choices, switching targets brought more benefit. If they didn't switch, this focus fire might be broken; if they switched, at least they could take out a chunk of Cruel Silence's health.

But Wu Qi, of course, hadn't prepared to just obediently stand there for Happy to grab. He had made such a decision, so how could he not have made some plans? He wasn't Steamed Bun, who just randomly walked step by step. He was a proper pro player, who took one step and looked three steps ahead.

So, the position he'd taken with this Shadow Clone Technique was carefully selected from the start. He was slightly closer to Lord Grim, so that when Happy switched, Lord Grim would attack first, and Jiang Botao would immediately have a chance to breathe. And he wouldn't immediately facing a pincer on three sides. He and Jiang Botao could cooperate to deal with this situation, making things a bit more difficult for Happy.

Lord Grim lifted his hand.

Grab!

Wu Qi saw it very clearly. He thought, Ye Xiu must be trying to throw his Cruel Silence away, and with that, Happy could continue to focus Empty Waves. As expected, Ye Xiu wasn't the type to settle with the way things were. He was an expert who created more opportunities from the options he was given.

But, how could it be so easy.

Wu Qi inputted controls as fast as he could. Cruel Silence moved horizontally. As he dodged, he wanted to lure Lord Grim toward him, to lighten up on Jiang Botao even more.

In his view, Ye Xiu had already taken the first step to switch targets. Then, no matter what, he wouldn't just give up again. Starting from this moment, he was leading Happy by the nose.

But to his surprise, when his Cruel Silence dodged, Lord Grim actually twisted back. That hand he extended ultimately landed on Empty Waves' body.

Fling!

Empty Waves was tossed outward, but he wasn't thrown far, he was in fact thrown very close. Lord Grim just twisted his body, and Empty Waves was sent flying toward the nearby Cruel Silence.

Fuck!

Wu Qi couldn't help but curse in his heart. Ye Xiu's actions turned out to be even more cunning than he'd expected. Choosing who to focus? Throwing far to get rid of interference? Not at all.

A feint to dodge Cruel Silence, and then he grabbed Empty Waves and threw him over here. If he crashed into Cruel Silence, then the two of them would be focused together.

How greedy! In your dreams!

Wu Qi immediately controlled Cruel Silence to jump backward. Empty Waves was right under his nose, but in the end, they didn't collide. But shortly after, Cruel Silence found himself flying forward outside of his control.

Fuck fuck fuck!!!

Only now did Wu Qi realize. This push and then dodge, had given the guys behind him enough time to catch up. Without waiting for him to make any controls, Cruel Silence had already been blasted down, the ground filling his vision. He suffered attack after attack from behind, and they even counted as back attacks. This clearly wasn't a typical sweeping attack. To be directly knocked down in one go, Wu Qi had already realized, this was the Tyrannical Chain Punch of Happy's Brawler…

A huge attack, not to deal with Empty Waves, but to knock over himself. Happy was actually planning to focus both of them at once. Wu Qi had delivered himself right to them to be eaten!

In the blink of an eye, cannon fire descended upon Cruel Silence and Empty Waves. Clearly, Happy was outputting damage toward the two targets together. It was a shame that the other three of Happy only had average AoE ability, but focusing the two opponents like this, it was clear that this boosted their overall damage output.

The broadcast displayed the total health of the two teams. Happy, who had been lagging behind earlier, used this bout of focused fire to successfully deplete Samsara's total health.

Could they directly take out the two of them?

Some of the greedier Happy fans were already holding these kinds of hopes, but this evidently wasn't realistic. This round of focus fire ultimately only lasted for a few moments. Steamed Bun Invasion knocked Cruel Silence to the ground and began to beat him up, but when Soft Mist arrived, she only managed one attack before Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf arrived before her. Moreover, Cloud Piercer's gunfire had never stopped, and this time, his Sharpshooter was already rushing toward them like a close-range attacker.

Chapter 1713 - Failure to Find a Path

Surprise wasn’t an element unique to Happy. Zhou Zekai had always been someone who performed astonishing feats.

Cloud Piercer fired his guns as he ran. He was closing the distance to increase his firepower. With a Slide Kick, he reached the limits.

Flip over and jump. Cloud Piercer dodged Soft Mist’s attack. As he flipped up, his guns roared with sparks. The bullets looked like sword stabs, but their speed was far faster than what any close-ranged class could achieve.

Blood burst into the air. Soft Mist, who was closest to him, wasn’t able to dodge and was hit by the bullets.

Firearm Martial Arts!

Zhou Zekai used another skill. Cloud Piercer kicked Soft Mist aside. Right now, he needed to break open the situation. He didn’t plan on focusing a single target. After kicking aside Soft Mist, he continued to shoot, while throwing an elbow at Steamed Bun Invasion.

Steamed Bun Invasion had just finished using Tyrannical Chain Punch, and didn’t think much of Zhou Zekai. With Tang Rou handling him, he felt like there was nothing to worry about, so he continued to focus on Cruel Silence. But Tang Rou was sent flying by Zhou Zekai, and without any pause, Cloud Piercer’s attacks rushed towards Steamed Bun Invasion.

Hua!

A huge object suddenly filled up Zhou Zekai’s screen. Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened, instantly blocking Cloud Piercer’s vision.

Screensaver attack!

Zhou Zekai immediately cancelled his attack and had Cloud Piercer retreat rapidly. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed into its spear form and gave chase. Suddenly, an Earthquake Slash swept across the ground, forcing Lord Grim to halt.

Boom!

An explosion sounded from the side. Sun Xiang coordinated with Zhou Zekai. With a Falling Flower Palm, One Autumn Leaf sent Soft Mist flying towards Steamed Bun Invasion and Lord Grim.

Steamed Bun Invasion dodged to the side, and as if he were taking revenge, he grabbed Cruel Silence with a Fling, and threw him over to One Autumn Leaf.

Sun Xiang had One Autumn Leaf dodge, but to his surprise, Cruel Silence suddenly stopped in midair and arced towards Cloud Piercer.

Circle Swing!

Cruel Silence was unexpectedly fished back by Soft Mist, who had just been sent flying by a Falling Flower Palm. Sun Xiang’s attack was neutralized by Tang Rou. Cruel Silence’s suddenly turn in the air was no less surprising than Steamed Bun’s erratic plays. Zhou Zekai’s attention had mainly been on Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. As a result, he wasn’t able to react in time. The two characters collided and crashed to the ground together.

The stadium was in an uproar. However, gunshots continued to be heard.

Cloud Piecer had collided with Cruel Silence. It had been too late for him to dodge, so Zhou Zekai finished his attacks. Bullet holes riddled Soft Mist’s body. Zhou Zekai’s extremely difficult gunshots had been sent entirely towards Soft Mist.

No, that wasn’t all!

“Delivery Gun!”

Countless people discovered that not only was Soft Mist hit by the bullets, she was fixed in the air. Only a Delivery Gun could achieve this. Under those circumstances, just hitting the target was already hard enough, but also completing a Delivery Gun that required extreme precision and speed? It wasn’t something a normal person could even imagine being able to do.

However, Zhou Zekai had done it!

The crowd had gone wild, seeing Cloud Piercer and Cruel Silence collide. A short moment later, ear-deafening cheers echoed across the stadium.

Sure enough, Zhou Zekai was the unrivaled protagonist of this stage.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!

Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf unleashed a Rising Dragon Soars the Sky. His Evil Annihilation transformed into a powerful dragon, letting everyone know the significance of Zhou Zekai’s feat. Soft Mist, who was held into place by the Delivery Gun, became finest delicacy for the dragon. There was nowhere for her to run.

Boom!

Battle magic erupted, affecting Steamed Bun and Ye Xiu as well. They were too close to the center of the attack. The light blinded their vision, becoming a form of cover for Cruel Silence and Cloud Piercer.

Get up!

Zhou Zekai used Quick Recover to avoid the knockdown effect. Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence had been grabbed by Circle Swing, so he couldn’t use Quick Recover. However, after getting knocked to the ground, he immediately got up at a speed faster than the average player’s Quick Recover.

Cruel Silence didn’t retreat. He rushed towards the exploding magic. Empty Waves’ wave slash also swept towards the blinding light.

Focus!

Samsara was focusing on a target.

Even after so many back and forths, they were able to maintain their focus on Soft Mist!

With this burst of attacks, Samsara regained the overall health lead on Happy.

Samsara maintained this health lead as their focus on Soft Mist continued.

They ignored Dancing Rain’s artillery fire. They ignored the pincer from Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion. Their attention was only on Soft Mist. It was as if they didn’t know what going too far meant, as they greedily focused on killing Soft Mist.

What’s going on?

Samsara was playing beautifully, but no one thought that they would be able to kill Soft Mist in one burst. However, Samsara didn’t think the same.

Nebula Wave Slash!

Samsara showed their confidence in themselves.

The Spellblade skill came from Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves. Magic burst out, enveloping Soft Mist and separating her from the others.

Steamed Bun Invasion raised his arms and threw a Brick at Empty Waves.

Pa!

The Brick was shattered into pieces by Nebula Wave Slash. This high-level skill wasn’t going to be broken so easily.

In that case, Poison Needle!

In that case, Molotov Cocktail!

Steamed Bun Invasion had a lot of tools that he could use, but in everyone’s eyes, it was all a waste of time. Not a single one of the skills was able to break through Nebula Wave Slash. Steamed Bun refused to run. He was going to stay right there and leave his stupidity behind.

Sand Toss… he was still continuing.

What’s the point? Everyone thought to themselves. But suddenly, Jiang Botao began to get worried.

As Steamed Bun Invasion attacked, he turned to look at the other side, which was where Lord Grim was located.

Sure enough!

Lord Grim was beginning to move.

Jiang Botao didn’t know if Steamed Bun was faking his stupidity, or if he actually was just stupid, but he did know that Ye Xiu wasn’t stupid. As a result, it didn’t matter whether Steamed Bun was being stupid, the important part was what Ye Xiu would do in this situation.

Steamed Bun Invasion kept throwing out pointless skills, but they were only pointless because Jiang Botao was paying attention to them. When he dealt with these attacks, the other areas of Nebula Wave Slash would be sparser, and holes in his defense might appear.

Lord Grim was taking advantage of these distractions to make his way through. Sure enough, Ye Xiu knew how to seize opportunities.

Beat them at their own game?

Jiang Botao suddenly thought.

No…

In the end, he gave up on the idea. He decided that he was going to handle this situation in the most reliable way possible. He knew that Ye Xiu couldn’t be up to any good, and Ye Xiu was far more experienced and skilled than him in complicated scenarios.

As a result, Empty Waves kept a low profile as he dodged the Sand Toss. The Nebula Wave Slash silently crept towards Lord Grim’s side. He didn’t increase his offensive threat excessively. He was just patching up any previous gaps.

Lord Grim stopped moving. Sure enough, that was where Ye Xiu had intending on breaking through. Ye Xiu tried to search for another way in, but he quickly discovered that Jiang Botao wasn’t making any excessive adjustments. He was only dealing with the problems at hand.

This is… going to be difficult!

More adjustments meant more choices. More choices meant more strategies. With more strategies, it was more likely for him to find a way in.

However, when the changes in a situation were limited, only one option became available.

It was easy to walk along a single path, but there was also only one exit. And if the other side was ready for them at that only exit?

This definitely wasn’t a path that Happy wanted to tread upon, which was why Ye Xiu wanted to try an alternate path.

But in the end, Samsara had sealed off this alternate route.

Even worse, they weren’t given any opportunities to try again.

Chapter 1714 - Low Health Is No Big Deal

Jiang Botao was glad that he didn’t make any unnecessary choices. He was glad that there was only one path remaining for Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun to take.

Dodge! Minimize the damage taken from Nebula Wave Slash. This was already the best that they could do. Break past Nebula Wave Slash and interrupt their focus fire? Impossible. There was no time left. Samsara was doing everything they could to kill Soft Mist. With every passing second, her health plummeted.

Happy only had one chance to find another path, but they had failed. Of course, they could try again, but Soft Mist likely wouldn’t survive long enough.

Dodge!

Jiang Botao watched Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion closely. He didn’t relax. Once they finished killing Soft Mist, their attention would shift towards them.

Who to kill first?

Jiang Botao observed the movements of the two characters, but as he did so, he noticed that something strange had entered his sight.

What is it?

Under the protection from his Nebula Wave Slash, what could possibly make its way in?

Grenade?

Jiang Botao’s pupils suddenly contracted. He had no time to think. A portion of his Nebula Wave Slash cut towards that grenade.

The grenade exploded. The sound wasn’t loud, and the light wasn’t flashy. However, an almost tangible shockwave could be seen diffusing from the center of the explosion.

Implosion Grenade!

Cloud Piercer, One Autumn Leaf, Cruel Silence. It didn’t matter how powerful their characters were. The shockwave pushed them back.

Jiang Botao’s heart went cold. He turned around and saw Dancing Rain. She was very close, much closer than before.

Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun failed to break past his Nebula Wave Slash. They had failed because Jiang Botao had noticed their intentions in time. However, he hadn’t realized that the path they sought didn’t end there. The path extended from Steamed Bun to Ye Xiu to Su Mucheng…

Pull his attention away and create an opening for Su Mucheng to sneak in an Implosion Grenade through the Nebula Wave Slash.

No, that wasn’t all.

He wasn’t the only one who hadn’t noticed the Implosion Grenade. None of the others on Samsara had noticed it either.

He had been distracted by Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun. Because of their efforts, a hole appeared in his defense.

But what about the other three on Samsara?

It was Tang Rou and Su Mucheng.

Soft Mist faced their assault, while Dancing Rain helped from afar. Their goal wasn’t just to break the siege. From the start, there had been another goal as well. They were narrowing Samsara’s vision towards one direction.

This sort of cover…

This was one of One Autumn Leaf’s and Dancing Rain’s signature techniques back in the day. Every team used it as teaching material, showing how teamwork between a close-ranged and long-ranged character should be done.

This sort of technique was very discreet. The close-ranged characters caught inside would be completely unaware. Jiang Botao was a certain distance away, and he would have noticed it if not for Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun distracting him.

“That’s why a Sharpshooter being too close is never a good thing.”

If Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer had been attacking from afar, this technique wouldn’t have escaped his notice. Ye Xiu typed in the chat as Lord Grim charged towards Cloud Piercer.

Cloud Piercer didn’t stop his attacks even as the Implosion Grenade pushed him away. He was still attacking Soft Mist to try and lower her health even further. In the end, Samsara wasn’t able to finish off Soft Mist in one go. However, the outcome wasn’t bad. Soft Mist only had 28% of her health left, the lowest among those remaining.

Samsara might be able to kill her with one more wave of attacks.

If they continued their attacks onto Soft Mist, it should be easy for them to suppress Happy.

Thus, Samsara’s next move should center around Soft Mist.

These were all very logical thoughts. This was the advantage of a health lead, and the disadvantage and burden of having less health. Without a healer, these advantages were laid bare. Relying on Lord Grim’s healing wouldn’t change anything.

Samsara still had a clear lead.

That was what everyone thought at first, but these thoughts only lasted a second.

Because the one with the lowest amount of health was Soft Mist, and the player behind her was Tang Rou.

That girl who declared a 1v3 the moment she entered the Pro League.

That girl who refused to compromise despite the storm of criticism towards her.

That girl who wanted to keep going even after a 1v3 in the finals.

Low health? So what?

Lord Grim charged towards Cloud Piercer. Soft Mist charged towards Cloud Piercer even more fiercely than Lord Grim. The Implosion Grenade had sent the three on Samsara flying, but the Nebula Wave Slash wasn’t affected. In reality, Soft Mist was still inside the Nebula Wave Slash, but the moment she was free from Samsara’s chains, she rushed out. She moved even faster than Cloud Piercer, who was still shooting at her. However, she didn’t retreat. The Nebula Wave Slash wrapped around her, continuously dealing damage, but she didn’t cower.

There were no longer any chains holding her back. She charged ahead. Her goal was to attack.

Her decisiveness reduced the amount of attacks that she took from Cloud PIercer. Her decisiveness allowed her to break out of the Nebula Wave Slash as fast as possible.

Attack, attack, attack!

Attack as defense?

Her thoughts weren’t nearly so complicated. She was still alive, so she had to attack.

The battle wasn’t over until she was dead. It couldn’t be called a battle without attacking. You couldn’t win without attacking.

Draconic Crusher!

Soft Mist swung her spear, Dancing Fire Flowing Flames, turning even the air itself red.

Tang Rou understood what sort of situation Soft Mist would be facing. In order to ensure that the battle wouldn’t become a 3v4, she should be more cautious, more defensive, fighting under the protection of her teammates.

That was how the vast majority of teams and players would handle this situation, especially in such an important match.

But not Tang Rou. Her personality was like a blazing fire. She didn’t like being careful or receiving protection. She wasn’t good at doing either of those things. If she played that way, it would be bad news for Happy. She would only be making things worse. She would become a burden.

Tang Rou understood this point, and so did the team.

Thus, Soft Mist charged forward and attacked.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim quickly coordinated with her.

Their target was Cloud Piercer. Without any hesitation, the two picked the same target.

Because Cloud Piercer was the only attacker who could keep dealing damage to Soft Mist. He needed to be suppressed quickly. Zhou Zekai was the most formidable player on Samsara too, and Tang Rou was more than happy to fight against him.

Draconic Crusher!

Cloud Piercer rolled to the side, but he was immediately welcomed by Lord Grim.

There’s an opening in the middle. Charge through!

Right when Zhou Zekai thought this, Steamed Bun Invasion appeared in front of him.

Unlike Ye Xiu and Tang Rou, Steamed Bun didn’t have a clear goal in mind. However, he would follow wherever his boss went. Steamed Bun was top-class in this regard. As a result, Steamed Bun wasn’t much slower in switching focus to Cloud Piercer. Ye Xiu moved fast, so he moved fast too.

Powerful Knee Strike!

In the blink of an eye, Steamed Bun Invasion reached Cloud Piercer. The opening was sealed shut. Zhou Zekai could only have Cloud Piercer quickly step back. He had to dodge this attack first. A Grenade seemed to accidentally slip out from his hands.

Boom!

The grenade exploded. Steamed Bun Invasion jumped back. Lord Grim dodged to the left. Soft Mist dodged to the right.

But Happy’s offense didn’t stop. Lord Grim used Sword Draw. Soft Mist swept across with Tyrant’s Destruction. The two attacks intersected.

Forward, left, right, neither of those directions would do. Cloud Piercer could only continue retreating.

Boom!

Another Grenade exploded.

When Cloud Piercer “accidentally” left behind a Grenade, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim “accidentally” tossed a Grenade as well. The timing was just right.

Cloud Piercer was sent tumbling by the explosion. Even so, his two guns continued to spit fire, shooting bullets towards Soft Mist and Lord Grim.

The two dodged and attacked again. This time, every direction was sealed. Cloud Piercer was pincered in the middle. Zhou Zekai could only watch as Steamed Bun Invasion charge over and grab Cloud Piercer by the throat.

Strangle!

His defense decreased by 50%. It was the perfect opportunity to dish out damage. Dancing Rain’s artillery fire descended.

A cold light tore through the explosions. Samsara’s support had come. The first to arrive was Cruel Silence, starting with a “Rend.” The Level 75 skill sliced towards Soft Mist. Empty Waves’ Fire Wave Slash also swept towards her.

Regardless of Tang Rou’s mentality, whether she attacked or retreated, she was still Samsara’s main target.

Tang Rou showed no fear. She would fight one. She would fight two. She would fight whoever came her way. Health didn’t matter. She didn’t have time to worry about any of that.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Soft Mist used Dragon Breaks the Ranks at close distance. To get to Cloud Piercer, she forced her way past Cruel Silence’s Rend and Empty Waves’ Fire Wave Slash.

Cloud Piercer dodged. He raised his gun towards Soft Mist’s head. A Thunder Snipe at near point-blank range.

But before the snipe went off, his gun was knocked aside by Soft Mist’s spear.

Zhou Zekai was astonished. What incredible awareness!

The awareness to attack first! The awareness to deal as much damage as possible in the shortest amount of time!

Tang Rou knew that she would likely be the next to leave the battlefield. Before she left, she would do her best to injure Samsara and weaken them.

Empty Waves had the least health on Samsara. He was Happy’s most convenient target. Jiang Botao understood this point. He wasn’t as fierce as Tang Rou. He did what a low-health character should do. He kept his distance, and wasn’t overly aggressive.

As a result, Happy had to give up on focusing Empty Waves.

Tang Rou’s thoughts were simple. She wouldn’t let a single second go to waste. She wanted Soft Mist dealing damage every moment she was still alive.

Thus, she used Dragon Breaks the Ranks to get past Cruel Silence and reach Cloud Piercer.

Cloud Piercer moved to the side. Tang Rou didn’t want to continue wasting time with Dragon Breaks the Ranks. She immediately cancelled the skill, and chased after Cloud Piercer.

Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer had just taken out his sniper rifle. He was just about to aim, when more attacks arrived…

Chapter 1715 - The More Targets, The More Damage

Attack.

Soft Mist sent a storm of attacks towards Cloud Piercer. Cloud Piercer had already switched out his guns for a sniper rifle, indicating that Thunder Snipe had been used. However, he didn’t fire the shot, wasting the skill..

This was an extremely rare sight for Zhou Zekai. To Samsara’s fans, this was a grave matter, but to Tang Rou, it was nothing special.

72%.

Tang Rou glanced at Cloud Piercer’s health. She didn’t want to just interrupt his attacks. She wanted to take his life.

Of course, Tang Round understood that this goal was a bit out of reach, but the greater the challenge, the better.

Falling Flower Palm!

Her spear knocked aside Cloud Piercer’s weapon. With her other hand, Soft Mist followed with a palm.

Cloud Piercer retreated rapidly.

Wasting a high-level skill like Thunder Snipe was unfortunate. The skill had only just gotten off cooldown. However, Zhou Zekai made the right choice and cancelled the skill. He could have still gotten the snipe on a different target, but if he wanted to dodge Soft Mist’s attack, he could only cancel it.

Zhou Zekai felt the threat coming from Tang Rou.

He had been restrained under Soft Mist’s pressure, and took the initiative to give up on the snipe.

By cancelling the skill, Cloud Piercer was able to dodge the Falling Flower Palm. The sniper rifle was put away. With Wildfire in his left hand and Shattered Frost in his right hand, he aimed towards Soft Mist.

The two guns fired. Soft Mist crouched down. She was actually able to dodge the bullets at this distance.

Dancing Fire Flowing Flames pierced through the air, Dragon Tooth!

Cloud Piercer was already floating back. When he attacked, he had jumped back as well. He was using Aerial Fire to widen the distance between them.

Dragon Tooth missed. Double Stab!

Fiery red afterimages were left behind. Behind Soft Mist, a pitch-black light soared through the air.

Evil Annihilation!

Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf had been blown back the farthest by the Implosion Grenade. He had finally made his way back. His aim was still Soft Mist, the character with the lowest health.

Tang Rou sensed the attack.

She was familiar with Battle Mage skills, and she had exceptional hearing abilities.

It was a Dragon Tooth. It was faster, and it would interrupt her Double Stab.

But Tang Rou wouldn’t let it interrupt her though. Soft Mist continued with her attack. Dodging would affect Double Stab’s speed, and she wouldn’t be able to hit Cloud Piercer. As for One Autumn Leaf, Tang Rou was confident that someone would deal with him. Wasn’t Ye Xiu by her side? How could he not notice?

Tang Rou’s confidence in Ye Xiu was very reasonable.

Soft Mist’s Double Stab was faster. One Autumn Leaf’s Dragon Tooth was even faster. But the fastest was still Lord Grim.

Sun Xiang saw a blur, and a figure suddenly appeared in front of him. The figure didn’t stop as if he were just passing by. However, the weapon in the figure’s hands collided against Evil Annihilation. With a gentle ring, his Dragon Tooth was knocked askew.

Shining Cut!

Lord Grim was moving while attacking, blocking One Autumn Leaf’s attack. As soon as he knocked aside the Dragon Tooth, his umbrella transformed into its gun form. Bang bang bang, three Anti-Tank Missiles fired towards Cloud Piercer. Then, he turned and jumped, using Collapsing Mountain towards One Autumn Leaf.

In the blink of an eye, he chained together three attacks while moving. When he jumped up with Collapsing Mountain, everyone was still looking at the Shining Cut colliding with One Autumn Leaf’s Dragon Tooth! Lord Grim’s attacks were faster than what people could keep up with.

Boom boom boom!

The three Anti-Tank Missiles exploded. Soft Mist’s Double Stab hit, and the three Anti-Tank Missiles also hit. Cloud Piercer fell to the ground and rolled to neutralize the knockback from the attacks. Tang Rou didn’t let go. Soft Mist continued to give chase. On the other hand, Lord Grim’s Collapsing Mountain was dodged by One Autumn Leaf, who followed with a Tyrant’s Destruction at both Lord Grim and Soft Mist. Lord Grim stepped to the side. He placed the sword form of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella in front of him. Guard!

Lord Grim slid back. The Tyrant’s Destruction was blocked by Guard, and naturally wouldn’t be able to reach Soft Mist.

Soft Mist’s assault continued. She showed no mercy, repeatedly using skills. Magic Chasers continued to fly. For a moment, Zhou Zekai was suppressed by her. Cloud Piercer was forced to dodge most of the time.

Samsara’s fans were dumbstruck. They weren’t used to seeing such a sight.

He was being suppressed?

No…

Not exactly. Zhou Zekai could fight back, but he chose not to. He was intentionally controlling the distance between Cloud Piercer and Soft Mist, waiting for the right moment.

Cruel Silence.

Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence had finally come back after being sent flying by Dragon Breaks the Ranks. As a teammate, he quickly understood Zhou Zekai’s intentions. He didn’t charge directly at Tang Rou. He was waiting for the right moment, where he could kill Soft Mist in one move.

Cruel Silence rushed back. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves was constantly adjusting his movements. Zhou Zekai was waiting for an opportunity where the entire team could coordinate with each other.

Now!

Cloud Piercer suddenly raised his two guns. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves swung his shortsword, Divine Chains. Cruel Silence brandished his dagger and suddenly accelerated.

Oh?

Tang Rou sensed it.

One, two, three…

Are they all coming?

Perfect. Her DPS against three targets would be higher than against just one target, no?

Tang Rou sensed Samsara’s intent. She wasn’t afraid, though. She didn’t run away. Instead, she thought of it as an opportunity to deal even more damage. To her, Samsara’s focus-fire was like a bunch of little minions taking the initiative to group up for her.

One Wave Rush!

Soft Mist rushed forward, swinging her spear. Wisps of fire would occasionally leap into the air.

She continued to attack. Even if the enemy side was focusing her, she didn’t retreat.

Perhaps it was brave, or perhaps it was reckless. But this was indeed the best way that Tang Rou could help the team win.

No one in Happy stopped her. Dancing Rain, Steamed Bun Invasion, and Lord Grim, who was fighting against One Autumn Leaf and supporting her from time to time, all three of them were coordinating with Soft Mist.

Soft Mist had the lowest health on the battlefield. She was the easiest target for Samsara to put Happy on the defensive. But in Tang Rou’s hands, Samsara was welcomed by Happy’s most formidable counterattack.

More targets meant more damage to deal! Tang Rou took the logic from the game and placed it into a pro match. Zhou Zekai? Wu Qi? Jiang Botao? Even if there were more, she wasn’t afraid! It was too bad that Sun Xiang couldn’t join in!

Kill!

Tang Rou didn’t have a set target. Her only goal was to deal as much damage as possible. Soft Mist’s health fell rapidly, but the damage that she dealt was far more than the damage she took.

The last one!

Most of her skills were on cooldown. She only had a few hitpoints left. This attack would be her last.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!

Her final attack was this Level 70 skill. Fiery magic gathered in the shape of a dragon. Wu Qi saw his screen turn scarlet red. The attack was aimed at him.

Dodge!

He had to dodge. However, Steamed Bun Invasion was aggressively pouncing at him. Dancing Rain’s artillery fire was raining down. The others on Happy supported Tang Rou’s final attack with attacks of their own. Cruel Silence had nowhere to run. But at this moment, Wu Qi saw what his teammates were doing.

Light Wave Slash!

Burst Firing!

Empty Waves and Cloud Piercer had sent out extremely fast attacks. Wu Qi saw Soft Mist’s health.

They can!

These two attacks could kill Soft Mist, but the question was whether the attacks would kill her before the Rising Dragon Soars the Sky hit him.

Which one would be faster?

The attacks on both sides were fast. Wu Qi wasn’t sure what the answer was. He only knew that he should try and win as much time as possible, even if it was just by 0.1 seconds!

Cruel Silence tried to gain as much time as possible by moving away. But the Rising Dragon Soars the Sky finally arrived. The fiery dragon was just about to swallow him.

Hit!

Light Wave Slash hit.

Cloud Piercer’s Burst Firing had also hit.

I’m saved!

Wu Qi was elated. However, Cruel Silence was still engulfed by the magic.

How?

The magic burst apart. Cruel Silence’s health dropped violently. He found it hard to believe. He wasn’t sure which of the attacks was faster, but he knew that the two attacks were more than enough to kill Soft Mist!

Yes, more than enough.

Soft Mist remained standing in the same posture after using Rising Dragon Soars the Sky. Her health had dropped to zero.

Soft Mist had fallen, but traces of holy light remained on her.

Traces of healing…

Lord Grim’s healing was for moments like these.

Chapter 1716 - The Result Isn’t Too Good

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim healed at the last moment. He wasn’t able to save Soft Mist’s life, but the additional health was enough for Soft Mist to survive until the Rising Dragon Soars the Sky hit Cruel Silence.

Magic exploded outwards. This was her final glimmer of radiance. Her health had fallen to zero, but the damage from this attack was fully realized.

Is she dead?

Samsara’s players didn’t dare to be certain. Soft Mist’s health had indeed fallen to zero, but she was still standing, holding her final stance with Dancing Fire Flowing Flames pointed forward.

Just to be sure, Zhou Zekai fired another shot.

The bullet hit Soft Mist. She didn’t make any movements to dodge. The momentum of the bullet knocked her down.

Dead…

Soft Mist had fallen. Tang Rou’s viewpoint was rising into the air. Just like this, she saw Soft Mist fall to the last bullet.

So this is it.

Tang Rou let go of her mouse.

Unfortunately, she wouldn’t be able to fight until the end. However, this feeling of putting in everything she had wasn’t bad.

We’ll win!

Tang Rou was filled with anticipation. She realized that her confidence in her team was probably greater than her confidence in herself.

We’ll definitely win! She believed firmly.

However, there weren’t many people who thought the same as her.

Too reckless.

Whether it was Samsara’s players or the spectating pro players, even Happy’s Fang Rui and Wei Chen, when these experienced players viewed Happy’s play from a normal logical standpoint, they felt like Happy had indeed been reckless.

A nearly dead character threw caution to the wind and actually became even more aggressive. And her teammates? They didn’t stop her. In fact, they supported her.

Everyone agreed that this play had been a powerful show of force. Tang Rou used her 28% health to inflict damage totaling much more than 28% to Samsara.

Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer went from 72% to 51%.

After Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence ate that final Rising Dragon Soars the Sky, his health dropped to 32%.

The loss in health from these two characters was much more than Soft Mist’s 28%.

However, no one had died. That was an extremely big difference.

If all of that damage had been focused on Cloud Piercer or Cruel Silence, Happy might have been able to bring one of them down. In that case, Tang Rou’s last stand would have been very successful.

However, even though she had dealt a significant amount of damage, after losing her, Happy was now at a numbers disadvantage.

Looking at their health values, Samsara’s side: Cloud Piercer – 51%, Cruel Silence – 32%, One Autumn Leaf – 70%, Empty Waves – 40%.

Happy’s side: Lord Grim – 71%, Dancing Rain – 82%, Steamed Bun Invasion – 81%.

For Samsara, their health totaled 193%. For Happy, their health totaled 234%.

However, Samsara had an extra person.

This numbers advantage was enough to wipe away that bit of difference in health. An extra player meant an extra source of DPS, an extra source of attack or defense, an extra variable to consider.

If you asked a pro player, or even a normal player, to choose a side in this situation, 99% of them would choose the side with an extra player, rather than the side with one fewer player but more total health.

Moreover, it hadn’t been Happy’s choice to be the latter. The circumstances had forced it. They obviously knew that a numbers advantage was much more valuable than a health advantage.

Even though the outcome wasn’t the best and Happy seemed reckless, no one felt like this recklessness was inappropriate.

If they hadn’t been reckless, what else could they have done?

Focus a character and trade Soft Mist for someone on Samsara?

How could Happy not have wanted a trade instead? It was clearly because there was no such opportunity to do so. The conditions weren’t there.

Tang Rou wasn’t Fang Rui. If it were Fang Rui, this master of playing dirty, he would have been able to survive with 28% health for a very long time. However, stalling wasn’t Tang Rou’s specialty. Battle Mages were useless from far away. That was why she chose to go with what she was best at.

Attack!

Tang Rou fought until the last moment. In any case, injuring Samsara was better than sacrificing herself for nothing. Moreover, her frenzied offense could have potentially opened up opportunities. Samsara had endured a huge amount of pressure in order to kill her.

Good thing she only had 28% of her health!

After finally killing Soft Mist, Wu Qi’s first thought was to celebrate. If Soft Mist had a bit more health, if Tang Rou had kept up that frenzied assault for any longer, Cruel Silence may have died along with her.

Good thing…

No, not just good, things couldn’t be better.

They had endured Tang Rou’s final stand and finished off Soft Mist. They had the numbers advantage now. Their situation was great.

What next…

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was still fighting with One Autumn Leaf. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain was rather far. In his eyes, Steamed Bun Invasion was the most annoying enemy. If not for that bastard’s interference, he would have certainly been able to avoid that Rising Dragon Soars the Sky.

Go die!

Cruel Silence brandished his dagger, Heart-Piercing Stab!

Wu Qi could almost hear Steamed Bun’s anguished cry when the dagger struck his heart. But when he looked, Steamed Bun Invasion had run away.

Heart-Piercing Stab missed. Wu Qi was in a daze for a good second.

In a pro match, one second wasn’t short. One second was enough to do all sorts of things.

Because Wu Qi really hadn’t expected Steamed Bun Invasion to turn and run.

Cruel Silence only had 32% of his health left. He had the lowest health on Samsara. In theory, shouldn’t Happy be focusing him next? Even if Happy wasn’t in a hurry to, Steamed Bun Invasion was so close to him. It would be extremely convenient for Steamed Bun Invasion to attack him! Even if really did intend on running, shouldn’t he at least attack once before running?

But Steamed Bun Invasion ran away immediately, free and at ease.

Was he scared?

During this one second, the thought had come up for only a brief instant before he abandoned it.

Scared?

It wasn’t hard to see a player’s personality from how their characters moved. This Steamed Bun, let alone him, he didn’t even give a fart about Zhou Zekai. He was just that carefree, doing whatever he wanted, not caring about anyone else. For example, right now! If you’re going to run, shouldn’t you at least attack a bit first!

During this one second, Steamed Bun had run quite a bit. When Wu Qi came to his senses again, Steamed Bun was helping Ye Xiu fight Sun Xiang.

One Autumn Leaf, the healthiest character on Samsara.

What the fuck is he thinking?

Wu Qi truly didn’t understand.

Chapter 1717 - Breakthrough

Wu Qi simply couldn’t understand Steamed Bun’s actions. However, for the viewers, Steamed Bun ignoring Wu Qi was actually quite logical.

His Steamed Bun Invasion had been positioned close to where Soft Mist was killed. Cloud Piercer and Empty Waves could easily switch targets to Steamed Bun Invasion and form a pincer. Along with support from Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence, even if they failed to kill Steamed Bun Invasion in one go, they would certainly be able to injure him severely.

Steamed Bun was quite quick to catch on, and Steamed Bun Invasion quickly left his original position. But still, throwing out an attack at Cruel Silence wouldn’t have delayed his retreat much. Throwing out an attack would have slowed down Cruel Silence’s pursuit as well.

Steamed Bun hadn’t attacked, but it didn’t hinder him in any way. By doing nothing, he actually confused Wu Qi. In fact, compared to throwing out a skill, this confusion hindered Wu Qi more.

Then, Steamed Bun Invasion began targeting One Autumn Leaf. Wu Qi didn’t understand this, and neither did the viewers. One Autumn Leaf had the most health on Samsara. As the side with the numbers disadvantage, Happy shouldn’t be going after him.

In contrast, the players on Happy understood why Steamed Bun had made this decision.

“If you don’t know what to do, just follow me.”

This was what Ye Xiu had told Steamed Bun in case Steamed Bun ever got confused.

Steamed Bun was doing exactly as he was told.

Wu Qi may have been stunned by Steamed Bun’s actions, but Zhou Zekai and Jiang Botao weren’t.

Steamed Bun Invasion’s speed had been surprising, but the two had ranged attacks. Just because the target had suddenly moved unexpectedly didn’t mean that the target would immediately escape from their attack range. There was still time to adjust their aim.

The pincer from Samsara’s Sharpshooter and Spellblade quickly formed.

Cloud Piercer shot after Steamed Bun Invasion, while Empty Waves made predictive attacks with his wave slashes to obstruct Steamed Bun Invasion’s movements.

By then, Wu Qi had come to his senses again. Cruel Silence immediately gave chase. However, at this moment, Dancing Rain’s artillery fire aimed towards him.

Steamed Bun’s target switching was a what-do-I-do decision. After all, the advice “if you don’t know what to do, just follow me” wasn’t exactly the precursor for brilliant teamwork. As a result, Su Mucheng didn’t go and support Steamed Bun. Happy’s next target should be Cruel Silence, who had the lowest health on Samsara, not One Autumn Leaf. That was a certainty.

As a result, Su Mucheng threw everything she had at Cruel Silence.

However, just her alone wasn’t efficient enough. Between Zhou Zekai and Jiang Botao, the whole was certainly greater than the sum of its parts. Although Steamed Bun Invasion had more health than Cruel Silence, the two would likely be able to kill him first. Even if both sides completed a trade, Happy already had one fewer player to begin with.

Samsara had been unwilling to do a trade before, but now, they were more than happy to take it. When one side had the numbers advantage, the other side would only be willing to make a trade if there was no other choice.

Happy needed some sort of change to happen. If they continued like this, they would definitely lose.

Happy didn’t want this situation to last, but Samsara definitely did. They were more than content with the current circumstances.

Between Cruel Silence and Steamed Bun Invasion, no one knew who would be the first to fall. However, Sun Xiang stopping Ye Xiu was extremely important as well. If Ye Xiu was let loose, who knew what he would do.

Don’t think you can get past me!

Sun Xiang was determined. He had been waiting for the day where he would completely defeat Ye Xiu. Being unable to defeat him had cast a shadow on his heart. This shadow bound him, stifled him. Even when he won, he never felt like he was truly happy. He would always think to himself, if it were Ye Xiu’s One Autumn Leaf, would things have gone differently?

Now, he understood that One Autumn Leaf didn’t only just possess a powerful strength. One Autumn Leaf was a symbol of invincibility, the Battle God that had swept the Alliance. Even when Ye Xiu’s later achievements weren’t as good as before, he still had to bear that burden. Let alone Sun Xiang, who, after taking the account, had been relegated and defeated in the Challenger League. His achievements had been beyond terrible.

There was no way that shadow wouldn’t exist on him.

Inheriting a new account card was as simple as having that account in your hands. However, inheriting a character, especially one such as One Autumn Leaf, was the same as inheriting its former glory. It was a pressure that would bear down on the inheritor.

Sun Xiang had underestimated the significance behind what the character symbolized. He had thought that he could easily do better. But reality wasn’t nearly as simple as he had imagined.

He had experienced failure after failure, growing under the weight of this pressure.

One Autumn Leaf, the invincible Battle God.

He might not be able to emulate this glory, but he refused to be crushed under its weight.

He might not be able to beat Ye Xiu, but he wasn’t going to let him get past so easily.

Sun Xiang saw Lord Grim dodge. Lord Grim was planning on quickly changing directions to get to his side. He swung his spear, Tyrant’s Destruction!

Lord Grim was forced to a stop. Then, he changed directions again!

He moved extremely fast, perhaps even fast enough to outspeed the Tyrant’s Destruction.

But the Tyrant’s Destruction vanished. Sun Xiang reacted extremely fast. As soon as he saw Lord Grim respond, he cancelled Tyrant’s Destruction and chased after him with a different skill.

Falling Flower Palm!

He stepped forward and pushed out a palm, using his entire body to block Lord Grim. In an instant, Lord Grim had no way to move forward.

A watertight defense.

No one could point out any faults. Sun Xiang had let go of his ambitions. He was no longer trying to defeat Ye Xiu. Right now, his only goal was to hold his ground and prevent Lord Grim from getting past him. This unprecedented level of concentration was making him play at an unprecedented level of skill.

Falling Flower Palm shot out.

This attack didn’t seem to just be a wall. It didn’t seem like Lord Grim would even be able to dodge it.

Lord Grim could only try and parry it.

Falling Flower Palm!

Lord Grim also threw out his own Falling Flower Palm. However, he had acted later. The power of his Falling Flower Palm couldn’t compare to One Autumn Leaf’s. Lord Grim was slightly weaker in attack power than One Autumn Leaf too.

Boom!

The two palms collided. The friction between the clashing magic let out violent sounds. With both characters using the same skill, Lord Grim was losing to One Autumn Leaf as expected. He wasn’t sent flying, but he kept sliding back. His two feet left two ditches in the ground.

But at this moment, the eyes of many of the experts lit up.

Chance!

Widening the distance was a good way to get past an enemy’s blockade. Lord Grim had numerous movement skills in his kit. It wouldn’t be hard for him to circle around One Autumn Leaf.

Sure enough, Ye Xiu saw the opportunity as well. Lord Grim retreated back a bit before steady himself, Charge!

He didn’t use Charge towards One Autumn Leaf. Instead, he moved diagonally. He was clearly planning on going around.

One Autumn Leaf stepped to the side, extending his spear to its limit. One Autumn Leaf was attacking at his maximum range.

Circle Swing!

This high-priority grab skill stabbed towards Lord Grim.

Not enough time.

The experts with accurate judgement could tell that there wasn’t enough time for Lord Grim to change directions and dodge. Sun Xiang was too focused. His reaction speed was too fast. His calculations were completely on point.

He could only change directions!

If Lord Grim turned, he would need to cancel Charge. Relying on adjusting his trajectory wouldn’t be enough to dodge the Circle Swing.

But even with this turn, he wouldn’t be able to dodge this Circle Swing. However, instead of a turn, it was more like a jump to the side.

Shining Cut!

An Assassin skill. A cold light flashed. He was planning on outspeeding the Circle Swing. Then, he would change directions and break through.

That was what everyone thought. However, after the Circle Swing missed, Sun Xiang quickly followed with another attack.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

One Autumn Leaf used this high-level skill, pressing forward in close pursuit.

Right angle turn?

Impossible. No angle would be able to avoid this Dragon Break the Ranks. The hitbox of the attack wasn’t just the tip of the spear. The powerful clash between the battle magic and the surrounding air were all hitboxes for this skill.

Stop and go backwards!

Lord Grim didn’t make a right angle. He didn’t look for an angle. He stopped and ran back.

This sort of high speed displacement tested the opponent’s reaction speed and hand speed. However, Sun Xiang was extremely focused right now. He was able to quickly sense even the smallest changes and respond promptly.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks, turn!

Tang Rou often changed direction mid-attack, and Sun Xiang could do it as well. With this turn, Lord Grim happened to be caught.

Too late. Sun Xiang’s reaction speed and hand speed was too fast. There was no time for Ye Xiu to react and respond.

Ye Xiu failed to break through…

Countless people gripped their hearts as they watched this scene. At this moment, their hearts sank. The outcome was plain as day.

Yes, the outcome was plain as day.

Lord Grim and One Autumn Leaf brushed past each other.

He dodged it???

The crowd went into an uproar. Many of the pro players were stunned. They were impatiently waiting for the slow-motion replay to be shown.

The slow-motion replay appeared.

After One Autumn Leaf adjusted the direction of his Dragon Breaks the Ranks, had there been no openings?

No. Lord Grim moved the moment One Autumn Leaf changed direction. He had moved in the opposite direction. He had changed direction as well.

Colliding Stab.

Another movement skill. Lord Grim and One Autumn Leaf brushed past each other. In that instant, the two looked like they were touching, as if they were a pair of Siamese twins. But in the blink of an eye, the two passed by each other in opposite directions.

Dodged?

Sun Xiang was stunned. He had left no openings with Dragon Breaks the Ranks? No. It was Lord Grim’s final change in direction that hadn’t left any openings.

After changing the direction of Dragon Breaks the Ranks, there indeed hadn’t been any openings. But what about before? Lord Grim had seized an opening before the change. Ye Xiu had realized that there was room for him to adjust, so he did it ahead of time. There hadn’t been any openings after adjusting Dragon Ranks the Ranks, but there were openings before…

Chapter 1718 - Screensaver Coordination

He broke through!

The two characters dashed past each other. By the time Sun Xiang cancelled Dragon Breaks the Ranks and turned around, Ye Xiu had already run quite far. Lord Grim didn’t wait for the Colliding Stab to finish before switching to a different skill.

Slide Kick!

It was also a movement skill. Although it was slower than Charge and Colliding Stab, Slide Kick was a Gunner skill, meaning that he could start shooting from afar with his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella in its gun form.

Floating Bullet, Stun Bullet.

Both skills could disrupt a target’s offensive tempo, and couldn’t be ignored. Zhou Zekai had noticed Lord Grim’s movements, however. Both shots were dodged by Cloud Piercer.

Now that Lord Grim was closer, Zhou Zekai prepared himself for a fight with him. Then, he saw Lord Grim shoot upward, jumping while in the middle of Slide Kick.

Using a skill to its completion made it easy for the opponent to predict. Cancelling a skill was a technique that every pro player was adept at. It was necessary to create mix-ups.

Ye Xiu cancelled the Slide Kick ahead of time. The airborne Lord Grim swung his arms.

Ninja Tool – Smoke Bomb.

A cloud of purple smoke quickly spread, enveloping Cloud Piercer inside and blinding him. Zhou Zekai had Cloud Piercer hastily escape from the Smoke Bomb’s range. But by the time he got out, Lord Grim had disappeared.

He’s inside the Smoke Bomb…

Zhou Zekai didn’t need to ask to know the answer. Cloud Piercer immediately started firing at the smoke cloud. However, Ye Xiu clearly didn’t have any grand or complicated plans for this Smoke Bomb. He simply used it as cover so that he could continue forward without interference.

His target was Cruel Silence!

Lord Grim’s target was obvious. He dashed into the Smoke Bomb from one end and dashed out from the other end. His Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed into its gun form, firing two shots towards Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves. A message popped up in Happy’s chat at the same time: “Steamed Bun, follow me!”

Not just him, but Steamed Bun as well. The entirety of Happy was going to focus Cruel Silence.

Happy’s intentions were clear. Next, Samsara would need to respond. Zhou Zekai and Jiang Botao didn’t immediately rush over. They moved to the left and right, keeping their distance as they continued to attack. Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf had been shaken off by Lord Grim earlier. He had already turned around, and was now giving chase. However, Smoke Bomb covered a large area. Would Ye Xiu not have done anything to it? Lord Grim had low-level skills from all classes. It was likely that he placed down a few Thief traps or Ninja Caltrops.

But Sun Xiang didn’t hesitate. One Autumn Leaf rushed into the smoke, and then out of it.

He didn’t meet any obstacles as he dashed through the Smoke Bomb. Sun Xiang didn’t know whether he was just lucky, or if Ye Xiu hadn’t placed any traps. He only knew that circling around the Smoke Bomb would delay him, widening the distance between One Autumn Leaf and Lord Grim even further. This was what Ye Xiu wanted.

If that was what the enemy wanted, then he had to do his utmost to do the opposite. It was a very simple but effective principle to follow in a competitive match. The fastest way to catch up was to directly charge through the Smoke Bomb, so that’s what Sun Xiang did even if it did mean charging into the unknown.

I’m out!

As soon as he got out from the Smoke Bomb, his vision cleared. Sun Xiang’s heart pounded. Ahead, Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence was ready for what was to come. He was heading towards Sun Xiang to meet up with him. Zhou Zekai and Jiang Botao were flanking from the left and right. It was a classic offensive cross formation. This was Samsara’s response. Right now, they weren’t afraid of a clash with Happy because they had an extra player over them.

Charge!

One Autumn Leaf didn’t slow down. Sun Xiang felt regretful that he had just used Dragon Breaks the Ranks, otherwise, his opener would have been even fiercer. But his other option was no weaker than Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!

One Autumn Leaf used Soft Mist’s final move before her death. The magic dragon formed from Evil Annihilation was black as it roared and rushed out.

Whether it was Lord Grim or Steamed Bun Invasion, neither of them could afford taking the hit. Sun Xiang wasn’t hoping for the attack to land. His goal was to tear apart Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion’s suppression of Cruel Silence. Cruel Silence didn’t have much health to begin with. If Happy’s three characters focused him, it wouldn’t take long for him to die, and Samsara needed to maintain their numbers advantage. If Samsara lost their numbers advantage so easily, their health disadvantage would be much more apparent.

Zhou Zekai and Jiang Botao upped their aggression. Maintaining their numbers advantage was the priority, but lowering the enemy’s health was extremely important as well. It would serve as a foundation for future changes.

The attacks from different areas converged towards the center.

Cloud Piercer and Empty Waves were long-ranged. Happy couldn’t do much to stop them. Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion had originally planned on pinning down Cruel Silence and then quickly killing him, but One Autumn Leaf’s Rising Dragon Soars the Sky couldn’t be ignored. One left, one right, the two dodged. An opening appeared. Wu Qi had been waiting for this opening, and immediately seized it. He moved in the opposite direction of the Rising Dragon Soars the Sky to break past Happy.

Dragon Raises Its Head, or even Dragon Turns Its Head?

When Samsara’s fans saw Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf use Rising Dragon Soars the Sky, they had a feeling of hope.

But their hopes were extinguished.

After rescuing Cruel Silence, Sun Xiang unexpectedly cancelled the Rising Dragon Soars the Sky. The Level 70 skill had failed to hit its target, so he gave up on it.

Much of the crowd felt that it was a pity, but the pro players knew that Sun Xiang cancelling the skill was the most effective usage of it. His goal wasn’t to attack the enemy, but to protect Cruel Silence.

By cancelling the skill, the ending lag wouldn’t be as long. One Autumn Leaf leapt forward.

Despite being caught in the pincer from Cloud Piercer and Empty Waves, Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion had no choice but to turn around and continue chasing after Cloud Piercer. It didn’t seem like they had any better options.

Double Stab!

One Autumn Leaf attacked both targets simultaneously. Cruel Silence took this opportunity to get behind One Autumn Leaf. Wu Qi was planning on resetting the tempo and re-establishing his offense. He wasn’t as reckless as Tang Rou. He wanted to establish himself a support behind One Autumn Leaf.

Dodge!

One left, one right. Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion refused to let go of Cruel Silence. One chased from behind, while the other tried to circle to the front. One Autumn Leaf looked like he was being treated as a wall. Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t seem to pay too much attention to Cloud Piercer’s and Empty Waves’ attacks either.

Samsara had the numbers advantage, but Happy had their own advantage: more health.

Because they had more health, they were willing to trade their health for a more impactful outcome. As a result, they were willing to take the damage.

I don’t think so!

Ye Xiu had gotten past Sun Xiang once. This time, Sun Xiang would need to stop both Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun from getting past him. There was Su Mucheng interfering as well. It wouldn’t be too far-fetched to consider this a 1v3.

But Sun Xiang’s conviction was firm. He was going to be this unbreakable wall, and let Wu Qi finish switching to his new role.

He placed Evil Annihilation in front of him. Suddenly, Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion switched places.

Switch places?

Sun Xiang was confused.

Why?

To dodge? With this switch, the two dodged the attacks from Cloud Piercer and Empty Waves.

But…

Do you think I’m nothing but air? Switching places in front of me. Do you think I’m dead?

One Autumn Leaf acted.

But Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion acted even faster.

They weren’t switching places, but attacking!

Their target: One Autumn Leaf!

Trade health to hold them off?

The thought crossed Sun Xiang’s mind. After all, his One Autumn Leaf was relatively healthy. He could hold them off for a bit.

But he quickly threw the thought aside. Lord Grim and Steamed Bun both had control skills. Relying on trading his health to hold them off wouldn’t work.

He needed to attack to hold them off. He needed to attack to stall for time. Weren’t Lord Grim and Steamed Bun trading their health? In that case, he would attack to consume even more of their health.

Dragon Rises from the Sea!

With a tremble, magic splashed around Evil Annihilation like water.

Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella immediately opened with a whoosh. He was going to face Dragon Rises from the Sea with the umbrella’s shield form. At the same time, the canopy crashed towards One Autumn Leaf.

Shield Strike?

The skill could inflict Dizzy. It had to be dodged. One Autumn Leaf hastily retreated.

The umbrella canopy immediately retracted, and a hand reached out.

Steamed Bun Invasion, Strangle.

“Careful!” Sun Xiang’s teammate warned him in the team chat.

Sun Xiang didn’t panic. It was a Shield Strike. He had noticed it, and had been ready for it. One Autumn Leaf dodged to the side.

Steamed Bun Invasion’s outstretched hand grabbed nothing but air, but One Autumn Leaf was still held by the throat. Lord Grim’s Strangle…

After retracting the canopy, Lord Grim transformed the umbrella into its tonfa form. Lord Grim’s hand seemed to follow the length of the tonfa. It wasn’t as if Sun Xiang wasn’t wary of Lord Grim making an attack after the Shield Strike, but he hadn’t expected this sort of coordination.

One Autumn Leaf was grabbed by the throat, but Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t stop. His hand was still stretched out.

Not good!

Sun Xiang suddenly realized.

Lord Grim had lifted his umbrella, using its shield form as cover to grab One Autumn Leaf by the throat. And now, Steamed Bun Invasion was also using a shield to grab Cruel Silence’s throat. In his case, his shield was One Autumn Leaf.

Hit!

Cruel Silence had been sticking close to One Autumn Leaf, so most of his vision was covered by One Autumn Leaf’s back. Right when he made the realization, a hand reached out towards him.

No matter how fast Wu Qi reacted, he would be too late. Cruel Silence had been moving too fast. Whether he tried to stop or use a skill, he would run right into Steamed Bun Invasion’s grasp.

Boom!

A Satellite Beam descended from the sky.

Dancing Rain had no good opportunities to act, so Samsara had been relatively lax towards her. As a result, Su Mucheng was given the freedom to coordinate with Happy’s offense. A powerful high-level skill at the perfect moment, engulfing both One Autumn Leaf and Cruel Silence. Under the effects of Strangle, both their characters had their defense reduced by 50%.

As Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion Strangled their opponents, they punched and kicked as well.

Zhou Zekai and Jiang Botao immediately tried to separate them, but both Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion had activated Reinforced Iron Bones. There was no way to interrupt them. The battle had turned into a contest of DPS.

Chapter 1719 - Team Kiting

In terms of overall combat ability, Samsara was of course stronger. In terms of numbers, they were also one player up. But right now, Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun were each restraining one of Samsara’s players with a Strangle.

Strangle didn’t completely lock the target’s movements. One Autumn Leaf and Cruel Silence could still struggle and launch a few attacks. At the same time, during the Strangle, Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion could also continue to attack their targets.

Not only did Strangle lower the target’s defense by 50%, it also lowered their attack by 50%. And Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion? They still had Reinforced Iron Bones activated, which raised their physical defense by quite a bit.

To make a long story short.

Samsara’s characters were strong, they had one more player, but Happy, by using this Strangle to catch two of Samsara’s players, were able to match Samsara in terms of damage dealt.

Just a few seconds.

By the time Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence finally managed to escape from the Strangle, his health was already depleted.

Rend Kill Dodge Flash Exterminate!

In the end, he still tried to use a powerful attack, to make a final desperate attempt. But he only managed a “Rend” before his health hit zero.

In this one moment, because they hadn’t defended against Happy’s Screensaver strategy, because they’d been caught by two Strangles, Samsara’s numbers advantage was erased in the blink of an eye.

One Autumn Leaf, who had originally had a lot of health, had lost quite a bit in this one attack. However, overall Happy had been focused on killing Cruel Silence. Lord Grim had locked One Autumn Leaf in a Strangle, but his attacks had still primarily targeted Cruel Silence.

Cruel Silence was killed for good, and One Autumn Leaf had lost 20% of his health in these few seconds.

50%, that was how much health One Autumn Leaf had remaining.

In order to achieve this killing opportunity, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim and Steamed Bun’s Steamed Bun Invasion had shed quite a bit of blood as well. Afterward, they’d used Reinforced Iron Bones to boost the power of their attack. Lord Grim had lost 29% health, leaving him at 42%; Steamed Bun Invasion had lost 27%, leaving him at 54%.

Happy’s injuries were greater than Samsara’s, but no one would think that this exchange wasn’t worth it. Because Happy had successfully killed Samsara’s Cruel Silence, they successfully rebalanced the number of players.

Again!

Again, after Samsara took the lead and upper hand, Happy managed to catch up. Right now, Samsara’s fans were almost out of energy to scream. Again and again, they were excited, but again and again Happy dumped a bowl of cold water upon them. Now, their hearts were soaked through cold.

Now that the numbers were even, when they checked the character health on both sides, Happy was suddenly in the lead in this situation.

Dancing Rain still had 80% health. In this confrontation, she’d only lost 2%. Clearly, Samsara hadn’t pressured her very much.

As for Samsara, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer and Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves hadn’t taken any damage at all. Happy’s goal of killing Cruel Silence was simply too pressing. They had no time to split their attention elsewhere.

Even so, these two characters were at 51% and 40%. Compared to Happy, they didn’t have any great advantage.

Their advantage had perhaps come down to the slight advantage in battle ability that their characters had.

Attack!

Only attacking was the best use of battle ability. Having just escaped from the Strangle, One Autumn Leaf was swiftly retreating back, but the Evil Annihilation in his hand spun, creating a high-speed spinning vortex that twisted toward Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion.

Cloud Whirling Windstorm!

Sun Xiang had used a powerful Level 75 attack. Zhou Zekai and Jiang Botao’s characters were no longer floating in the distance.

Right now, the health of their three characters was just the difference between 50% and 40%, there was no need to distinguish further. The two of them closed in, strengthening their offensive.

Bullets and wave slashes criss-crossed, as though forming a defensive line in front of One Autumn Leaf, and at the same time attacking Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion as well.

Forward!

Reinforced Iron Bones lasted a much longer time than Strangle, so Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion both still had Super Armor. With their health advantage, they were even more fearless. They directly charged forward to focus One Autumn Leaf.

Dragon Tooth!

One Autumn Leaf’s Evil Annihilation pierced forward, surprising everyone.

Dragon Tooth had a Stun effect, and it could interrupt many attacks, but right now, Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion both had Super Armor. Aside from dealing a bit of damage, the Dragon Tooth would have no effect. What was the point?

“Dodge!”

But in Happy’s channel, Ye Xiu’s instruction jumped out. The Dragon Tooth ultimately stabbed toward Steamed Bun Invasion, and his message was to tell Steamed Bun to dodge.

Ye Xiu had clearly realized something, but Steamed Bun didn’t have this Glory knowledge. The warning was too late. It was too late to dodge. Sun Xiang’s attack was already very fast, and his reactions were fast as well. Attack landed!

Aside from a tiny bit of damage, no effect. Steamed Bun Invasion was still charging forward as fast as ever. At this moment, a Chaser shot forward. After landing, a Dragon Tooth would create a Neutral Chaser, everyone knew this, One Autumn Leaf’s attack seemed so normal. But Ye Xiu’s performance was even faster, more hasty. Lord Grim used a skill, suddenly accelerating.

Circle Swing!

Another of One Autumn Leaf’s attacks shot forward. This skill had grab priority, so even in Super Armor it needed to be dodged. Lord Grim could only step to the side, and One Autumn Leaf immediately raised his speed, swiftly running forward. The Chaser created wind around his legs; the Neutral Chaser boosted his movement speed to a new level. After dodging the Circle Swing, Lord Grim tried to give chase, but an Ice Wave Slash had already swept toward him, and Lord Grim was forced to stop again. Super Armor could not block the various statuses inflicted by magic effects.

In the blink of an eye, One Autumn Leaf was able to put distance between himself and Steamed Bun Invasion and Lord Grim. Ye Xiu had reacted immediately to try and stop him, but ultimately he still failed.

And so One Autumn Leaf ran, Happy’s two chased him, and Zhou Zekai and Jiang Botao attacked even more fiercely. When everyone saw this situation, they realized, wasn’t this just kiting? This was just a coordinated version, where it wasn’t the same person running away and launching long-range attacks.

Now, everyone understood why Ye Xiu had been so anxious to attack. One Autumn Leaf had pulled off a Dragon Tooth to create a Neutral Chaser. Without the speed boost from this Chaser, One Autumn Leaf wouldn’t have been able to run away so completely.

Now, the distance had been established. Even though Lord Grim had the advantage of movement speed, he was facing a pincer from both sides, and he would take damage if he tried to force his way forward. More importantly, Sun Xiang still had a technique up his sleeve that he hadn’t used!

Teleportation.

This was the skill that One Autumn Leaf had applied to Evil Annihilation today. Right now, it should be off cooldown, but Sun Xiang didn’t rush to use it. If Ye Xiu continued to chase him, One Autumn Leaf could rely on Teleportation to instantly increase the distance once more.

This kite situation wasn’t easy to break. Cloud Piercer and Empty Waves strengthened their assault, but they didn’t close the distance too much. They maintained the possibility of kiting. If Happy switched targets now, they wouldn’t gain anything from that, either..

Chapter 1720 - Puppet Coordination

The Glory players that were rooting for Happy truly felt disheartened right now.

Starting from today’s group arena, again and again, Happy lost the advantage to Samsara, and then again and again they tenaciously overcame their predicament and caught up. In the group arena, they achieved a result that allowed them to hold their heads high, but what about the team battle right now? Again and again, they chased after Samsara, but were immediately pushed into a new predicament. To always be the one playing catch-up, it was suffocating.

This kind of feeling, when would it end?

Happy’s fans weren’t feeling good, but Samsara’s fans weren’t in a good mood either.

Again and again, they had shaken off their opponents, but again and again their opponents had caught up. They’d suffered a heavy blow in the group arena, and they were terrified that such a reversal would reappear in the team competition now.

They hoped that Samsara could establish their win as fast as possible, but again and again, their advantage would be erased by Happy. This was clearly just a grassroots team, their players and characters were inferior, but Samsara’s fans weren’t reassured. In their hearts, the feeling of “we might lose” had already taken root.

Right now.

Samsara’s three completed a kiting formation, and for Happy this was a very difficult situation to break. But all that Samsara’s fans could think about was how Happy had repeatedly faced difficult situations head-on and destroyed the feelings of security in their heart. Now, no matter the situation, Samsara’s fans couldn’t relax.

Kiting situation, what would Happy do? Samsara’s fans could only continue to watch anxiously.

Turn fire.

In the end, Happy still turned fire.

The target was Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves. Not only was he the Samsara player with the lowest health right now, Spellblades also tended to be less maneuverable, and were easier to catch up to.

But it seemed that Samsara had been prepared for this change. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves was retreating, but he wasn’t in much of a hurry. Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf didn’t continue to run away – instead, he turned around and began to approach. He maintained the possibility of fleeing at any moment, yet at the same time he demonstrated an offensive stance. He was ready to take either course of action. And Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer was chasing Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion, becoming Samsara’s main damage output right now.

Happy wasn’t sitting around idle.

Dancing Rain’s cannon opening aimed at Cloud Piercer. The two long-ranged Gunners on both sides began to compete. While this was going on, the distances between everyone were gradually beginning to change.

The distance from Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion to Empty Waves.

The distance from One Autumn Leaf to Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion.

Dancing Rain’s support distance.

Cloud Piercer’s attack distance.

There was too much hidden within all of this. Don’t even mention the ordinary players, even the pro players couldn’t immediately analyze everything there was. The situation was very complex, but no one was discussing, because they were all staring at the match. They didn’t want to miss a single detail.

Dancing Rain’s and Cloud Piercer’s attacks never stopped.

Lord Grim and Empty Waves were also using the occasional skill.

But to these pro players, the situation seemed very still. Both sides were moving, but as they were moving, it seemed as though they had reached some kind of agreement, establishing a sort of equilibrium.

And in this equilibrium, there were many hidden conflicts. Audience members who didn’t have enough skill wouldn’t notice anything.

Zhou Zekai tried to lure Dancing Rain to come closer, but Su Mucheng didn’t fall for it.

Jiang Botao tried to use his attacks to separate Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion, but Ye Xiu countered it.

The equilibrium was still maintained, but judging from attacker and defender, Samsara still had the upper hand, and Happy was slightly more passive.

But at this moment, Steamed Bun acted.

Within expectations, and yet still outside of them.

Of the six people on the field right now, only Steamed Bun was a rookie. Such a delicate equilibrium wasn’t something that a rookie player could control, never mind a rookie player like Steamed Bun, who was always breaking rules and conventional thought.

With Steamed Bun here, such a delicate situation could not be maintained.

On and off the battlefield, every Glory fan who was watching this match, they were probably all thinking something like this. The three from Samsara of course believed this as well, as though it were an established truth. So they, with the initiative, purposely made the situation more complex and delicate. They believed that Steamed Bun would quickly lose grasp of the rhythm.

No one would feel that their way of thinking was wrong. But as it turned out, Steamed Bun kept up, and he kept up quite well.

Samsara’s players were at a loss, but if they changed the rhythm now they would be confusing themselves. They couldn’t make any big adjustments.

But those outside of the battlefield knew how Steamed Bun had done it.

Because Happy’s chat was flooded with directions.

With such detailed instructions, Ye Xiu was basically holding his hand to guide him. In this moment, to everyone’s eyes, Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion were both being controlled by Ye Xiu. One was controlled by his own hands, one was controlled by messaged orders.

Ye Xiu’s ability to focus on two things at once and his hand speed were both worthy of awe, and Steamed Bun’s precise execution of instructions was also thoroughly impressive.

He was acting like a puppet dangling from strings. But it was exactly because he wasn’t one that it was so unbelievable that he could complete the correct actions so accurately.

Did this count as teamwork?

Did this count as tacit understanding?

The audience was all stunned. Another scene that had never before appeared in Glory history was brought before their eyes by Happy. They didn’t even know how to characterize this thing. In terms of directions, the directions of Thunderclap’s Xiao Shiqin were already considered trivial, but now that they saw Ye Xiu’s directions to Steamed Bun, no one even thought of Xiao Shiqin. There was simply no comparison.

“Is there anything these guys can’t do?”

This was the only thought everyone had left toward Happy.

But whether or not this counted as a form of cooperation, the difficulty was certain. Ye Xiu was bearing a huge burden, and it wasn’t easy for Steamed Bun either to complete all of Ye Xiu’s instructions.

But at this moment, Ye Xiu used one sentence to end his puppeteering instructions.

“It’s up to you, Steamed Bun,” Ye Xiu said.

“Got it, watch me!” Steamed Bun responded.

A simple exchange, but it meant faith and trust. At first sight, it was actually quite moving. But all of the Glory players who saw this conversation were puzzled. They didn’t know what about Steamed Bun was worth watching. Was relying on Steamed Bun and his unexpectedness enough to solve this delicate situation? His unexpectedness, could Happy’s players grasp it?

Happy of course couldn’t grasp it either. Not even Ye Xiu, who had watched Steamed Bun grow all this time, or Tang Rou, who had grown alongside him. They were just a little more mentally prepared, a little calmer and nimbler at reacting to Steamed Bun’s strange actions. Grasp? Steamed Bun’s thought process and logic was impossible for anyone to grasp. Right now, Happy could only grasp the timing.

“Got it, watch me!”

After Steamed Bun replied, he immediately acted.

Chapter 1721 - Indistinguishable Shadow Steps

Brick!

Steamed Bun Invasion acted. So brash, so splitting, in this sort of calm equilibrium, this kind of attack was like someone harshly slapping a desk in the middle of a silent classroom.

Samsara’s three had been waiting for Steamed Bun Invasion to do something dumb. They had purposely built this situation because they believed that Steamed Bun couldn’t keep up with the tempo.

But Steamed Bun’s steady performance caught them off-guard. They didn’t have the spectator view, so they didn’t know how it was happening. Ye Xiu simultaneously controlling his own Lord Grim and giving instructions to Steamed Bun, and Steamed Bun completely understanding and completing them, something like that had to be witnessed to be believed. Even experts like Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao, and Sun Xiang couldn’t think of this possibility.

The Samsara players offstage were all very anxious. These sort of unknown situations would always catch them off-guard. They wiped the sweat from their foreheads for their three teammates onstage. Right now, they were like all of the Samsara fans. After seeing Samsara get the advantage time and again, and then Happy catch up time and again, there was no way they could feel unshakable confidence. They had a deep feeling of danger.

Steamed Bun Invasion finally acted.

This was the change that Samsara’s three players had originally anticipated. Although they were surprised that Steamed Bun could keep up with the rhythm at first, when Steamed Bun suddenly broke the rhythm, they weren’t in any panic.

The skill and experience of these three pro players were, of course, much higher than those of ordinary people. A single surprise wouldn’t throw them into confusion.

The Brick flew out.

They’d seen Steamed Bun Invasion beginning his attack in the forward direction, but this Brick was ultimately thrown horizontally, towards the character to the side of him, One Autumn Leaf.

One Autumn Leaf was going neither forward nor backward, he was just hanging around him. Because of this, Steamed Bun had been annoyed at him for a while now.

This Brick provoked shouts in the crowd.

But although this kind of trick was a bit like bullying, with the reaction speed and technique of a pro player, even if the trick worked, there was still plenty of time to recover and react to it.

One Autumn Leaf twisted slightly, letting the Brick go past him. Sun Xiang was carefully watching Steamed Bun Invasion’s movements. The guy was finally starting to act randomly. This was the opening they’d been waiting for.

The Brick missed, but Steamed Bun didn’t give up. A Sand Toss came toward One Autumn Leaf.

A needle was hidden in the sand!

Sun Xiang was paying close attention to Steamed Bun Invasion’s movements. Of course, he noticed the little trick in this Sand Toss. Steamed Bun had added a skill like Poison Needle or Paralysis Needle within the sand. Because of the nature of Sand Toss as a skill, under most conditions, people would simply control their character to turn their head to avoid being Blinded, while taking the small amount of damage. And so, some Brawlers would take the opportunity to hide another attack in the sand.

But if the trick was spotted, then of course it would lose its effectiveness. One Autumn Leaf dodged the two combined skills.

What next?

To be honest, many people were quite curious as to what kind of offensive Steamed Bun would pull off. Sun Xiang calmly waited for the next change.

Next, Steamed Bun ignored him.

On one hand, Steamed Bun had found him annoying to look at, so when he had the time, he threw some attacks at him. On the other hand, Steamed Bun followed Ye Xiu’s instructions very closely. Ye Xiu said to focus Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves, so Steamed Bun definitely wouldn’t change the main offense just like that.

Powerful Knee Strike!

The next attack didn’t go toward One Autumn Leaf again, but instead toward Empty Waves. Steamed Bun suddenly flew in that direction with his attack.

An opening!

Sun Xiang’s eyes lit up. Steamed Bun Invasion had hastily used an attack that didn’t fit in the battle tempo, instantly messing up the rhythm. Suddenly, there was a distance between him and Lord Grim. The distance wasn’t large, but in this delicate balance, this small distance was a huge rift.

One Autumn Leaf finally stopped keeping himself open to two possibilities. In this moment, Sun Xiang focused, and attacked! Having been waiting for an opportunity on the sidelines for so long, most of his skills were off cooldown.

One Autumn Leaf attacked, Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike!

The black Evil Annihilation darted out, leaving countless afterimages. Under One Autumn Leaf’s swift charge, it thrust toward that opening that Steamed Bun Invasion had left after his Powerful Knee Strike.

Sun Xiang’s goal was clear: to cut the connection between Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun. Samsara’s plan was also clear. In this moment, it wasn’t just Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf who launched the attack. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer also suddenly adjusted the gunfire he was exchanging with Dancing Rain to point in this direction, coordinating with One Autumn Leaf to disrupt Happy’s connections in one go. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves began to attack Steamed Bun Invasion, because the Brawler was the next target they wanted to kill.

It was just this tiny detail, the distance between two characters creating an opening. But in such a high-level confrontation, it became a situation that would decide life or death. Ordinary gamers didn’t even know what had led Sun Xiang to act, what had led Samsara to change their tempo. They didn’t even know what opportunity Samsara had seized.

Experts knew.

Not only did experts know this, they also knew that this opportunity wasn’t necessarily as beautiful as Samsara thought it was.

Because Happy was in control of this opportunity.

Steamed Bun suddenly changing rhythm was an opening for Samsara, but it was one for Happy as well. Since Happy controlled the timing, Happy had a small lead in seizing this opening.

Beat the opponent at their own game…

Those old veterans who had fought against Ye Xiu for many years all exchanged glances, exchanging this one thought.

This was Ye Xiu’s speciality.

When the opponent thought that they had control of the situation, in reality, Ye Xiu was always a half-step ahead, or one step, or even more.

Today, this lead was very small. It couldn’t even be considered a half-step. But, this was still a valuable lead.

The opportunity that Samsara had been waiting for was what Happy had been waiting for as well.

But Ye Xiu was the one controlling when this opportunity occurred.

The lead came from this point. And this tiny lead, how could Ye Xiu not use it well?

Lord Grim was already moving.

Shadow Steps!

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella shifted to the form of a sword in his hand. With a flicker, afterimages fanned out. But before they were even done doing so, the umbrella was already changing forms again, although it was still a type of sword.

Triple Slash.

Another weapon skill appeared.

Lord Grim’s afterimages swung their swords and moved, instantly criss-crossing each other, vivid and colorful. The audience felt their sight going blurred.

Real body, fake body?

Let’s put this question aside for now!

Everyone suddenly realized that they hadn’t even been able to count clearly how many afterimages Lord Grim had created with his Shadow Steps. He’d used Triple Slash while his afterimages were still appearing, but through the high-speed movement of the Triple Slash, the sword light and the afterimages all intersected, and everyone could only tell that there were countless Lord Grims swaying before their eyes.

“Five? Six? Damn!” Even top Blade Master Huang Shaotian was cursing. Even he didn’t dare confirm. This was too much of a blow to his pride.

They couldn’t even confirm the number, how could they confirm the target? Let alone whether the target was real or fake?

The three Samsara players were also completely unsure, but the arrow was drawn on the bowstring, there was no going back. The situation created by the slight opening was this. There was no more time to consider, and definitely no time to try a different strategy. After one step, after many steps, they could only clench their teeth and continue.

Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike!

Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf continued along his original path. His goal was to separate Steamed Bun Invasion and Lord Grim. Right now, there were countless Lord Grims in front of him, and Sun Xiang’s eyes were going blurry as well. Real body? Fake body? He didn’t have time to worry about that. Who cares how many clones you have, who cares how many are real or fake, I’ll attack them all!

The black Evil Annihilation didn’t hold back, harshly piercing toward Lord Grim.

But the afterimages of a Blade Master’s Shadow Steps and the clones of a Ninja’s Shadow Clone Technique were different.

Shadow clones were physical bodies, with health. Hit by One Autumn Leaf’s roaring Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike like this, there was a possibility that they would instantly be cleared off the battlefield. But Shadow Steps created illusions that didn’t have any health to them. When Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike pierced through, it was as though they were going through empty air.

This was undoubtedly a false body, but right now, Ye Xiu didn’t care that the opponent could use this method to distinguish real and fake. Because in just the blink of an eye, the afterimages could cross, and the one that had just been determined to be fake would be swapped to who knows what new position.

Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike pierced countless targets, but Lord Grim was still using Triple Slash.

One slash, two slash, three slash…

With his numerous afterimages from Shadow Steps, Lord Grim actually travelled through the Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike just like that, as though the Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike were also nothing more than an illusion.

It didn’t stop him, so it didn’t separate him and Steamed Bun.

The opening that Samsara had spotted ultimately went to Happy. It became an opening for Happy to attack.

One Autumn Leaf’s Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike missed completely.

Cloud Piercer’s fired bullets all hit air.

Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves stopped running away, and began to attack Steamed Bun Invasion. Steamed Bun Invasion arrived in front of him, but close behind was Lord Grim. The final slash of Triple Slash arrived right in front of him. The countless images of Lord Grim criss-crossed for the last time, as dazzling and dizzying as ever.

Which was real?

Jiang Botao couldn’t distinguish them, and that meant that he had no idea which strike he had to dodge.

Empty Waves was already using a wave slash, but it was aimed toward Steamed Bun Invasion. But in just the blink of an eye, Happy’s attacker had become Lord Grim.

Hit!

The final slash of Triple Slash hit, and this hit immediately allowed Jiang Botao to tell which image was real. Empty Waves’ Divine Chain spun and slashed toward this real body, but heavy firepower was already blasting down from the sky – Dancing Rain’s powerful attack had arrived.

“Steamed Bun, follow!” Ye Xiu shouted in the chat.

Steamed Bun Invasion had been the one attacking initially, but the attack that hit Empty Waves first was Lord Grim’s. Steamed Bun Invasion, in order to dodge that wave slash, had rolled to the side, but right now, after Ye Xiu’s summon, he was instantly darting back.

3v1 focus fire. Although Cloud Piercer and One Autumn Leaf were already chasing toward the backs of Lord Grim and Steamed Bun, Happy didn’t retreat.

Snatch the kill, fight for blood. At a time like this, they were competing in sheer DPS.

Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf swiftly charged forward, slamming down a Draconic Crusher.

This skill had high priority and knockdown. Its interruption of rhythm couldn’t be ignored, and so the two Happy players hurriedly dodged.

But, in fact, the midair One Autumn Leaf didn’t wait for the attack to be executed. Instead, he vanished.

Teleportation?

No matter how unconventional Steamed Bun was, he still had the judgment he was supposed to. He and Ye Xiu immediately moved again as they searched for One Autumn Leaf.

But a flash appeared before Su Mucheng’s eyes.

One Autumn Leaf, that silhouette with which she was incomparably familiar, had flashed in front of her Dancing Rain, blazing with murderous intent.

Chapter 1722 - It’s Up to You, Leave It to Me

A completely unexpected change.

Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf charged toward Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion, but it actually turned out to be a feint. In the end, he had teleported to attack Dancing Rain.

The awareness of ordinary gamers was not enough to understand this change.

Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain had always been the character on the field with the most health. Even after exchanging gunfire with Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer just now, her health was still above 70% right now. Aside from her, not a single other character had more than 50% health.

It wasn’t that Samsara didn’t know how important Su Mucheng was. From the very start, they had enacted a BOX-1 against her. Using such a targeted formation was evidence of how highly they regarded her.

But after that, the battle situation had kept changing. It wasn’t that they didn’t want to restrain Su Mucheng, it was that they didn’t have the chance to. All they could do was rely on the long range of Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer, when he had the time, to make things a little more difficult for Su Mucheng.

But to disrupt only when “he had time,” for Su Mucheng that posed no pressure at all.

And now, the battle on the other side of the field was reaching a critical moment. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves was being suppressed by Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion together. But while they were focusing on him, Samsara thought of going to suppress Dancing Rain. Viewers couldn’t understand.

They didn’t understand, but the pro-level experts all understood.

Why did they suddenly think of suppressing Su Mucheng? Because among Happy’s three, Dancing Rain’s DPS was the highest. Destroy her firepower and they could greatly suppress Happy’s offensive ability. And more importantly, suppressing Dancing Rain was easier than suppressing Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion. They just had to close in on her.

Sun Xiang completed it. Feint, then Teleportation, no one expected that he would actually switch targets to Dancing Rain.

Su Mucheng also grasped the key point immediately, and she hurriedly prepared a skill.

Jump back, Mounted Gun!

Dancing Rain had a lot of health, so she wasn’t scared. Mounted Gun increased her attack and defense. Su Mucheng wanted to use this to complete this wave of focus fire.

But, she was too slow.

After all, Sun Xiang had switched targets extremely suddenly, and his reaction and controls weren’t slow at all. Dancing Rain’s jump backward was already the greatest opening she could achieve with her speed and limits, but it still couldn’t compare to how fast One Autumn Leaf’s attack came.

Dragon Tooth!

The skill landed. Short and stiff, but it interrupted Dancing Rain’s Mounted Gun.

The attack began.

At the beginning of the team battle, the one who had set up a BOX-1 against Su Mucheng had been Sun Xiang. This sort of targeted strategy had to be practiced. Sun Xiang had a year and a half of experience playing with Su Mucheng on the same team, so his understanding of her was extremely comprehensive.

Dancing Rain’s firepower was swiftly suppressed. Relying on Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion alone, the DPS dropped drastically. Spellblades were a plate armor class, after all, with high defense.

The situation changed.

With only two people focusing him instead of three, Jiang Botao’s situation immediately became much easier. Happy was pincering with two players, and so was Samsara. Even though Happy had managed a first wave of attacks, sending Empty Waves’ health down to 24%, Jiang Botao and Zhou Zekai quickly established a counterattack against Happy’s vital point.

Cloud Piercer, Empty Waves, targeted Lord Grim!

With Sun Xiang’s Draconic Crusher feint, Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun had no choice but to dodge. Jiang Botao had seized this opportunity, suddenly beginning a fierce counterattack.

Wave Wheel Slasher!

Grab priority, an attack that couldn’t be parried by typical skills. Although Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim could use similar skills to block it, but he hadn’t done so because he and Steamed Bun had been worried about One Autumn Leaf’s Teleportation and from where his surprise attack would come.

But as it turned out, One Autumn Leaf teleported to attack Dancing Rain, and the one who launched the surprise attack was actually Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves. As Wave Wheel Slasher split toward Lord Grim, Empty Waves was moving and pulling away. His short sword Divine Chain darted forward nonstop, sending wave slash after wave slash.

Storm, Light!

Two of the fastest wave slashes short forward first, further targeting the gap, and then, Fire and Ice combined with the earlier Light Wave Slash to complete a Three Fold Wave, and then, Waltzing Wave Slash, sneakily hidden within.

Jiang Botao was no longer holding anything back, he was bursting forth with everything he got. If Nebula Wave Slash weren’t still in cooldown, he would be using that skill as well.

Five consecutive wave slashes formed a net, firmly trapping Lord Grim within.

Ye Xiu wasn’t fighting by himself, but at this moment, Steamed Bun next to him wasn’t able to give him any assistance. His Steamed Bun Invasion was attacking Empty Waves nonstop, but he wasn’t able to effectively disrupt him. As Jiang Botao avoided the attacks that Steamed Bun Invasion threw at him, he completed the surprise attack against Lord Grim.

The change of the battle situation had started from Steamed Bun, but he truly didn’t have a very clear awareness. And right now, when the situation changed again, Steamed Bun seemed very out of step. His actions, faced with Jiang Botao’s rationality and effectiveness, were completely negated.

Empty Waves’ health, 11%!

This was the price Jiang Botao paid in avoiding Steamed Bun Invasion’s disruption. Empty Waves was in critical health, but he used his consecutive wave slashes to trap Lord Grim.

It was just a moment. But this one moment was already enough.

Partnered control allowed the other’s skills to come off cooldown. Cloud Piercer once again prepared a Thunder Snipe.

A beautiful and flawless partnership. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves set up the net, and Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer carried out the true killing move.

Bang!

The sound of Thunder Snipe’s fire was ear-splitting. Cloud Piercer hadn’t been standing too far away, so when the shot came out, it arrived in an instant. There was no space at all to dodge, there was no time for any skill. One headshot, double damage. After a struggle of a battle earlier, Lord Grim’s health was at 31%, but a Thunder Snipe headshot from Cloud Piercer was enough to wipe that out.

Time seemed to come to a halt.

No one had expected that, in this moment, Samsara would use a killing move, a surekill killing move, directly targeting Happy’s most crucial character.

The stadium was filled with shouts.

Shock, excitement, regret, hatred… All sorts of emotions, all sorts of attitudes, they were all expressed in this instant.

Blood sprayed forth. This Thunder Snipe had simply been unavoidable.

But, someone blocked it!

Steamed Bun Invasion.

When the bullets came, the silhouette of Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly flew in front of Lord Grim. He frantically extended his body, desperately stretched his head. The distance was too close, the bullets were too fast, these were the only movements he had time to do.

Blood mist bloomed.

Steamed Bun Invasion’s head was already gone.

“Boss, it’s up to you!”

It’s up to you.

Ye Xiu didn’t know how many times he’d said these words to Steamed Bun. Everyone could hear the sort of cajoling tone behind these words. But Steamed Bun had always taken this sentence very seriously. If they said it was up to him, then he would work his hardest to do the best he could.

“Leave it to me!” He would always reply with such confidence, even if this confidence was baffling to everyone, including Ye Xiu.

But this time.

“Boss, it’s up to you!” Steamed Bun said to Ye Xiu.

“Leave it to me!” Ye Xiu answered.

Steamed Bun Invasion fell. Earlier, his health had also been whittled down, and the powerful sniping headshot from Cloud Piercer directly dealt him 34% damage. Just like that, Steamed Bun Invasion left behind this final sentence that Ye Xiu often said to him, and he didn’t get up again.

Ye Xiu’s reply, he saw it.

“Go, Boss!!” Steamed Bun shouted in the channel, but with his character already turned into a corpse, he had no way of sending the message.

Shadow Clone Technique!

Ye Xiu didn’t waste the opening that Steamed Bun had sacrificed himself to obtain. Lord Grim directly pierced through the crack in the wave slashes.

Cut-Throat!

The true Lord Grim flashed behind Empty Waves and sliced forward with his blade, but Jiang Botao’s reaction speed was very fast. The moment he saw Steamed Bun Invasion moving, he was already making his next moves.

Roll!

Ahead of him, there were still ongoing damage-causing areas left behind by the sweeping wave slashes. Jiang Botao trusted that Lord Grim had no way to force his way through there to attack him. While rolling, Empty Waves’s sword stabbed backward.

Earthquake Slash.

The attack was concealed, the distance was close, the rippling energy didn’t even disturb the surface of the dirt. The “earthquake” effect swept Lord Grim.

“Fuck, how dirty!!” On the sidelines, Fang Rui was jumping on his feet and cursing. Normally, Chen Guo definitely would have given him a disdainful look. This kind of technique was exactly like what Fang Rui loved using.

But right now, Chen Guo was in no mood for that. She was so nervous that she couldn’t make a sound.

Even she knew how crucial this attack was.

Steamed Bun Invasion was directly killed, so killing Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves was too crucial. Only by quickly attacking him could they recover from the numbers disadvantage.

But Ye Xiu actually failed. Jiang Botao’s reaction speed and awareness was even faster than a rabbit in this moment. He avoided Lord Grim’s Cut-Throat, and instead rolled and hit Lord Grim with an attack of his own.

“Happy’s going to lose…”

A number of people had already drawn this conclusion. This was an absolutely critical match point, and Happy had missed it.

Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves rolled and climbed and leapt along the ground. Cloud Piercer’s cover followed him, the gunfire preventing Lord Grim from advancing further.

Right now, there was no way to force his way further. After getting hit by Earthquake Slash, Lord Grim had only 29% health remaining. Facing Cloud Piercer, who still had 32% health, in addition to the 35% health One Autumn Leaf, Ye Xiu could no longer let Lord Grim loose without a care.

Helpless, Ye Xiu could only use the cover of the map features, dodging Cloud Piercer’s attacks and steadily approaching Dancing Rain’s position. Samsara hadn’t been in a hurry, so they’d chosen to deal with Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim first. Now, Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves didn’t have much health remaining, but he was still rushing toward Dancing Rain. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer, after seeing that Lord Grim posed no more deadly threat to Empty Waves, also turned the majority of his firepower towards Dancing Rain.

Su Mucheng’s situation was getting more and more difficult. A Launcher who was closed in on by a close-range attacker was automatically on the defensive, and could even be said to have already lost half the battle. And right now, she was about to face a three-person focus fire from Samsara.

Seeing this kind of situation, countless people had already written off Su Mucheng as dead. Even if Dancing Rain currently had the most health out of all the characters, this would quickly become a fact of the past.

Was it over?

No!

Seeing how Ye Xiu was still resolutely searching for ways to rescue her, how could Su Mucheng think of giving up?

Chapter 1723 - Forward, Step by Step

In the outside world’s discussions of Glory, whenever Su Mucheng was mentioned, Ye Xiu would always be brought up as well. In the eyes of countless people, he was the sole reason for Su Mucheng’s accomplishments.

However, in Season 8, after Ye Xiu’s departure from Excellent Era, Su Mucheng’s performance put her in a new light. Everyone began reexamining her, evaluating whether their past opinions of her had been unfair.

Su Mucheng had changed the way people viewed her, but she never cared about any of it. All of her efforts to improve were because she believed that Ye Xiu would definitely return, and when he did, she needed to be ready. She needed to become an even better support for him.

Although she hoped to win the championships as well, she wanted to win it together with Ye Xiu. Otherwise, the victory would feel hollow.

She would never give up!

She was determined. Even if Ye Xiu gave up first, she would remain here and stand guard. But Ye Xiu never gave her this chance. Even when he was kicked from Excellent Era and had to start from zero, he cut his way through thistles and thorns to stand on top of this grand stage.

For victory.

For the championship.

These phrases always felt flat when describing Ye Xiu, because he did not lack victory. He had the most championship titles in all of Glory. Even so, he still blazed with unsurpassed passion.

Everyone felt like there must be some reason behind his drive.

Such as, to prove to Excellent Era that he could still play?

But if that was his reason, then he had already proved it. He had left Excellent Era, and then eliminated them in the Challenger League.

Yet even after all that, he didn’t change.

His actions, his performance, everything he did showed that the only thing he strove for was victory, pure victory. Whether it was Excellent Era or anything else, he didn’t seem to particularly care. In his eyes, there were only opponents. Opponents that he needed to defeat in order to win. Since that was the case, he just needed to defeat them. It was that simple.

There was no other reason that could explain Ye Xiu’s passion for Glory.

He had three championship titles and countless other individual honors, yet his goals remained the same: victory, championship.

There was no reason to give up. There was no excuse to give up. The championship was right in front of him.

However, in this regard, everyone believed that Samsara was closer to the championship than Happy.

Victory or defeat would be decided here!

Everyone watched the match attentively, Whether it was Samsara’s fans or Happy’s fans, all of them had their fists clenched tightly.

Looking back on this match, starting from when the two sides first made contact, there hadn’t been any cushions. The fighting and killing had begun beneath this golden pyramid, and it looked as if it was going to end there too. This was supposed to be a map filled with features; not far from there was a river, and next to the river was a forest…

However, after the two sides began fighting, they never strayed far, because there hadn’t been any opportunities to. From the start, both sides held onto each other tightly, not giving the other even the slightest room to breathe.

Now, the deciding moment had come.

The players seemed to have felt lit. Jiang Botao had the lowest amount of health on the field, but he was as lively as ever. After escaping from Lord Grim’s attacks, he began searching for Dancing Rain.

Earthquake Slash!

He had sent out multiple consecutive wave slashes at Lord Grim to trap him. As a result, he didn’t have many wave slashes left to use. Earthquake Slash was the lowest level wave slash and had the shortest cooldown. As soon as it came off cooldown, he immediately used it again.

Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer covered him from behind so that he wouldn’t be at risk of an ambush from Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. At the same time, this cover separated the connection between Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng.

The situation was looking good for Samsara, but none of them relaxed. Sun Xiang became increasingly focused. He paid attention to each and every movement from Dancing Rain, especially her cannon. In this situation, Su Mucheng definitely wanted to attack Empty Waves, who only had 11% of his health left. She wouldn’t even need a powerful high-level skill to kill him. Just a few normal attacks would be able to blast him off the stage.

But there were no opportunities for her to do so.

Sun Xiang clung tightly onto her. Not only was she unable to escape, even when she found an opportunity to attack, Sun Xiang would always knock her cannon askew at the last moment.

An Earthquake Slash swept by.

Dodge.

Every pro player, every player would have this thought as soon as they saw the attack. But Su Mucheng didn’t plan on dodging. She wanted to do more, not just wait for Ye Xiu to break open the situation.

Not only did Dancing Rain not dodge, she ran straight into the Earthquake Slash.

Sun Xiang was surprised for a brief moment, but he immediately realized that Su Mucheng wanted to use the knockback from Earthquake Slash to widen the distance between them.

Sun Xiang didn’t stop her. One Autumn Leaf immediately moved to the side, predicting which direction Dancing Rain would move towards.

But with this slight change in positioning, Dancing Rain raised her gun.

You want to attack?

Even though Sun Xiang was guarding her retreat path, this didn’t mean that he would neglect the possibility of Su Mucheng attacking.

Evil Annihilation flew towards her.

The instant the cannon flashed with light, the cannon was knocked askew.

One Autumn Leaf’s defense towards her was extremely tight. Why else was Su Mucheng unable to provide any support to Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun?

Previously, Sun Xiang had been completely focused on suppressing Dancing Rain’s attacks. Now, he was also thinking about killing her.

The Earthquake Slash struck Dancing Rain. However, One Autumn Leaf had already cut off her retreat path.

Falling Flower Palm!

One Autumn Leaf threw out a palm. The knockback from Falling Flower Palm was much stronger than that of Earthquake Slash. Not only did the palm stop Dancing Rain’s momentum, it even sent her flying in the other direction.

Su Mucheng didn’t care about all of this. She once again aimed at Empty Waves.

But Empty Waves was already charging towards her.

Jiang Botao didn’t let Empty Waves’ low health hold him back. He knew that victory could be decided here. Even though Empty Waves had almost no health left, he was Samsara’s biggest advantage. As long as they could suppress Dancing Rain and block Lord Grim, victory would be theirs. How could he cower at such a moment? Just having an extra player on the field wasn’t an advantage. The advantage depended on how the extra player performed.

The target was a Launcher. The closer he was, the safer he would be. Spellblades required a bit of space to use their skills, but since his opponent was a Launcher, he wasn’t afraid of fighting up close.

Colliding Stab.

Jiang Botao’s Spellblade could use this low-level Berserker skill as a movement skill as well. Empty Waves tread along the path created by Earthquake Slash. In the blink of an eye, he arrived in front of Dancing Rain.

Bang!

Dancing Rain’s cannon was knocked away by the Colliding Stab. Dancing Rain was once again unable to shoot in time. After getting sent flying by Falling Flower Palm, she was reflected back by the Colliding Stab. One Autumn Leaf was already waiting.

Dragon Tooth, Double Stab, Sky Strike…

Skills chained together, Chasers flew in succession. Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf performed a full combo. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves wandered to the left and right, slashing at Dancing Rain with what close combat skills he knew.

Launchers were poor at close combat. Facing this pincer from two sides, she became even more helpless.

It looks like it’s up to Ye Xiu!

Everyone’s gazes shifted towards Lord Grim. Everything depended on how fast Ye Xiu broke out from Cloud Piercer’s imprisonment. Hoping for a Launcher to escape from two enemies in close combat would be too difficult.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim didn’t stop moving.

At the start of the match, Team Happy had gotten a bird’s eye view of the map from on top of the pyramid. As a result, they had a slight advantage in the beginning. Qiao Yifan had utilized this advantage to escape from Wu Qi’s pursuit.

However, the battle had gone on for a long time now, with all of it revolving around this one area. Samsara’s players wouldn’t neglect the terrain. At this point, they had a good understanding of the terrain as well.

Particularly so for Zhou Zekai. His Sharpshooter required vision to attack, so he naturally need to pay attention to this aspect. Which areas were favorable for cover? Which of these areas allowed for movement? How could he get around these covers? He had to know the answers to these questions.

Lord Grim moved about, but his movements were limited. Zhou Zekai’s blockade was too tight. Zhou Zekai had originally been focusing Dancing Rain, but now, most of his attention had returned to Ye Xiu. It had to be said that Samsara was truly quite fearful of Ye Xiu. Despite it being a 3v2, they didn’t dare fight head on.

“That’s not the only reason.” Li Yibo heard Pan Lin’s analysis of the situation and added in his own opinion. “Don’t forget that Happy has a one point lead because of the group arena. If Samsara wins the team competition with only one player remaining, the match will have to go overtime to break the tie. If Samsara wants to directly win, they need to win with at least two players alive.”

“Oh, overtime… if they go into overtime, which team do you favor?” Pan Lin asked.

“Samsara, of course,” Li Yibo replied without thinking, “Have you not noticed that Ye Xiu’s playing has been getting worse and worse?”

“Oh, really?” Pan Lin was stunned.

“The pace of the team competition has been too fast. As soon as the two teams met, they began fighting. They didn’t move to a different area, or slow down the pace. Both sides have been attacking fiercely non-stop. For an older player like Ye Xiu, the burden is too much.”

“Is that so. But I really couldn’t tell! That Shadow Steps combined with Triple Slash from before was incredible!”

“The burden on him has only increased because of how incredible it was! He had to perfectly link together two skills while switching weapon forms. That must have been extremely difficult to execute. After making the play, he wasn’t given any moment to breathe. He had to keep it going. Just thinking about it is making my hands cramp…” Li Yibo said.

“Ah…” Pan Lin looked at the screen, at Lord Grim, who was constantly looking for an opening under the pressure from Cloud Piercer’s gunfire. He didn’t know what to say.

“Overtime is unfavorable for Happy. They definitely cannot let this go into overtime,”

Li Yibo said.

“In that case, wouldn’t it be a good idea for Samsara to drag out the match into overtime?” Pan Lin said.

“No, you can’t think about it like that. Samsara has an opportunity to end the match right here. Why would they give up their advantage to play in an uncertain overtime game? Ye Xiu’s condition might be declining, but who knows what will happen in a match. Taking advantage of a lead that you already have is also extremely important,” Li Yibo said.

“That’s true. Then, right now…”

“If this situation doesn’t change, Samsara will certainly win,” Li Yibo said confidently, “The key lies in Ye Xiu and whether he can break through. It doesn’t look like an opening will just appear. He’ll have to force his way through.”

“Forcing his way through… That’s not really a good idea either, is it?” Pan Lin said.

“But what other choice does he have?” Li Yibo said.

Yes, no other choice.

Lord Grim didn’t have much health left. He would certainly lose quite a bit of health if he forced his way through Cloud Piercer’s attacks. Let alone whether he could successfully rescue Dancing Rain afterwards, even if he did, both of them would nearly be dead. The situation wouldn’t be much better than before.

But if he didn’t, it was extremely unlikely that Su Mucheng would be able to escape from Sun Xiang and Jiang Botao on her own.

Su Mucheng was trying her hardest. Even though she wasn’t able to fully break free, Dancing Rain was slowly inching towards Lord Grim.

One step, two steps, three steps…

But wasn’t it pointless?

Sure, she was slowly making her way there, but she wasn’t able to get away and make contact with Lord Grim. It was as if she knew that she couldn’t place in a running competition, but she persevered so that she would at least be able to complete the course.

Countless Su Mucheng fans closed their eyes, unable to continue watching. Among these fans was Chen Guo. It wasn’t that she didn’t want to cheer for Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng. It was just too difficult to watch. The sort of struggle, this sort of effort, but for what? What would the outcome be?

The pro players were also quiet.

Ever since the start of the match, they had never once stopped their discussion. But at this moment, even though the situation was clear as day, no one said anything. They couldn’t bear to. They were also pro players. While the players on stage were trying their hardest, they had no right to talk ill of them, even if those efforts looked stupid, even if those efforts seemed pointless.

“What are you waiting for? GO!!!” Someone was unable to bear it any longer and stood up. It was Team Blue Rain’s Huang Shaotian. Everyone knew who he was referring to. The only person who could change things was Ye Xiu.

Force his way through!

He had no other choice.

Would Ye Xiu be able to create a miracle with only 23% of his health left?

Forward!

Ye Xiu made his move. Lord Grim hadn’t been able to find any openings the entire time, when suddenly, he rushed out.

As expected!

Zhou Zekai had anticipated this would happen. This was the enemy side’s last chance. How could Ye Xiu give up so easily? But it wasn’t going to be easy for him to grasp it.

Shining Cut!

Lord Grim rushed out. Although it was his last chance, he didn’t panic. He at least waited for all of his necessary movement skills to come back up.

Shining Cut! The first step that he took was done with a movement skill.

Left? Right?

Zhou Zekai didn’t need to guess. His Sharpshooter had two guns. He could cover both options. Ye Xiu was aiming for speed. He would be testing the enemy side’s reaction speed.

A cold light flashed, and Lord Grim rushed outward. Ye Xiu could hear bullets whistling by. Did it hit or not? He couldn’t concern himself with the answer. From the moment he stepped out, the only things he sought were speed and mix-ups.

Speed alone wasn’t enough. Zhou Zekai was precise with his aim and exceptional at predicting the opponent’s next moves. Ye Xiu needed to constantly mix things up so that Zhou Zekai wouldn’t be able to figure out his pathing. Even though Zhou Zekai could cover two directions with his two guns, it wasn’t possible for him to cover every angle, even with Gun Shake.

After taking two steps with Shining Cut, Lord Grim changed directions.

Charge!

Another movement skill. These movement skills were all fast, but there were differences in the actual numbers. Switching between movement skills was a mix-up.

After three steps, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim could feel the bullets hitting him. Zhou Zekai was using Gun Shake. He wouldn’t look down on Ye Xiu, thinking that he could he fully predict his movements. He chose to use Gun Shake to spread his bullets around and increase his coverage.

Lord Grim had been hit.

However, since Lord Grim was using Charge, normal attacks wouldn’t be able to stop him.

Charge, three steps.

Ye Xiu could see Dancing Rain getting closer, but he didn’t grow impatient. After Charge, he didn’t immediately follow with another skill. He took a normal step.

To break through Zhou Zekai’s blockade, mix-ups were more important than raw speed. Slowing down was also a mix-up. When the bullets started focusing on Lord Grim, he suddenly sped up.

Colliding Stab!

Another skill. Lord Grim sped up.

Cloud Piercer’s bullets seemed to be coordinating with Lord Grim, keeping up with Lord Grim’s sudden acceleration and spreading out.

The bullets chased after Lord Grim, but they weren’t able to completely stop him. Lord Grim might be able to force his way through, but he would definitely lose health doing so. This was the outcome that everyone was expecting. But afterwards, could a nearly dead Lord Grim be able to rescue Dancing Rain? After breaking through Cloud Piercer’s blockade, would he be able to break apart One Autumn Leaf’s offense?

No one was thinking about the future. What everyone saw was two players refusing to give up. The former Best Partners had been separated, and at this moment, they were trying their hardest to regroup. Whether they won or lost in the end was a matter for the future.

Three consecutive movement skills. Even though he wasn’t moving in a straight line, Lord Grim had closed the distance by quite a bit. However, Ye Xiu knew that the farther he went, the more difficult it would be. By quickly rotating through his skills, fewer and fewer options became available for him, meaning fewer and fewer mix-ups. Zhou Zekai definitely knew this as well.

Slide Kick!

Next up was a Sharpshooter skill. In terms of speed, this movement skill couldn’t compare with the others. However, since it changed the user’s posture, from standing to sliding, it would be able to dodge a few attacks. Ye Xiu suddenly used this skill to slide forward in a straight line. As he slid along the ground, he could see the bullets whistling past him.

Zhou Zekai reacted immediately and readjusted his aim. Once Slide Kick was done, Lord Grim would have to stand back up. Zhou Zekai was waiting for this moment.

But as soon as he readjusted his aim downwards, an explosion suddenly engulfed Lord Grim.

Shadow Clone Technique!

Zhou Zekai quickly thought of this skill. He had been on guard against this skill the entire time. Ye Xiu had created an explosion to cover him. It was only for an instant, but this instant gave Ye Xiu more than enough time to complete a Shadow Clone Technique.

Cloud Piercer didn’t stop shooting, but as he fired, he also rapidly retreated. Zhou Zekai wasn’t sure if he would be able to interrupt the Shadow Clone Technique. He retreated back to widen the distance between them so that he could obstruct Lord Grim for longer.

Ye Xiu had been carefully setting up for this Shadow Clone Technique, and his preparations paid off.

The explosion only lasted an instant before vanishing. The shadow clone inside of it poofed into smoke. Lord Grim had closed the distance considerably. Fortunately, Zhou Zekai had predicted this would happen. Cloud Piercer had retreated fast enough, keeping Lord Grim within his sights.

Triple Slash!

This skill was finally off cooldown.

Speed and variation combined in one skill. This skill was nothing more than three movement skills in one. Ye Xiu had left it for last, using it as soon as it came off cooldown.

Sword light flashed, three arcs in quick succession.

Almost there!

Countless people were excited. Even though they knew that getting close to Dancing Rain and rescuing her were two entirely different matters, when they saw that the two would finally be able to meet after going through so many hardships, they felt that it was already worth it.

As for what came after, no one was optimistic.

Lord Grim only had 18% of his health left. Losing only 5% of his health forcing his way through Cloud Piercer’s blockade was already amazing.

As for Dancing Rain, she was helpless under the pincer from One Autumn Leaf and Empty Waves. Her health lead was already a matter of the past. She only had 21% of her health left.

Even so, Samsara didn’t relax. They readjusted their tactics. They weren’t going to let these two reconvene so easily. Cloud Piercer continued to retreat, pinning down Dancing Rain from behind. Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf began paying attention to Lord Grim, and prepared to fight him. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves began adjusting his distance. He had too little health left. If Samsara wanted to keep their numbers advantage, he couldn’t let him get killed so easily.

Zhou Zekai had been focusing on Ye Xiu the entire time. Sun Xiang and Jiang Botao were now paying attention to Ye Xiu too. They were making adjustments because of Lord Grim’s approach. However, they didn’t stop attacking Dancing Rain because of this. Only the tempo had changed a bit. In many people’s eyes, this sort of change was negligible. However, Su Mucheng had been waiting for this moment for too long. Dancing Rain acted. Under this pincer, under Samsara’s notice, they heard the boom of a missile descending from the sky.

Heat-Seeking Missile!

A killing move suddenly appeared, catching everyone off guard. The three on Samsara didn’t have time to think, and hastily began to dodge. However, while they dodged, they didn’t forget to attack, including Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer. He also aimed his gun at Dancing Rain and fired.

As for the spectators, they were completely stunned up until the mushroom cloud dissipated completely. Only then did the pro players faintly realize something.

Dancing Rain had been in a difficult position? Yes, an extremely difficult position. Every step she took required a tremendous amount of effort. However, she hadn’t been moving towards Lord Grim, but Cloud Piercer.

Lord Grim forcing his way through had been difficult? Yes, extremely difficult. He wouldn’t have forced his way through if he had any other choice. However, his goal hadn’t been to rescue Dancing Rain, but to force Cloud Piercer back.

The two on Happy were grouping the three on Samsara together.

Finally, Su Mucheng was the main attacker, and this time, Ye Xiu was the support.

Chapter 1724 - Legendary Finishing Blow

This had been planned from the very start.

Upon realizing Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng’s intention, the pro players instantly grasped the implications.

Su Mucheng had repeatedly positioned herself to attack Jiang Botao in order to lure him forward. When facing a Launcher, the closer you went, the safer it was. Any pro player who had close-range battle ability would have made such a choice at that time.

And Ye Xiu?

From the very beginning, when Lord Grim had been searching for openings and moving all around, he had already been starting to lead Zhou Zekai’s movements. Zhou Zekai knew where he should stand in order to have clear lines of sight around the obstacles in the way, so Ye Xiu also knew which obstacles he should use for cover if he wanted to lure Cloud Piercer to stand where he needed him to.

And then, charge, advance, approach.

In order to give Lord Grim more pressure, Zhou Zekai would naturally control Cloud Piercer to move back and maintain the distance between them.

No one could say that Samsara’s actions were wrong. Any player in their places, facing the same conditions, would probably react in the same way. No one had suspected that Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng were actually planning such an attack.

The instant the mushroom cloud rose up, the entire stadium was shocked.

No one had noticed the guiding crosshair when Dancing Rain initiated her attack. By the time everyone noticed, the Heat-Seeking Missile was already howling down from the sky.

Dodge?

That was only one type of instinctive reaction when faced with an attack. In order to avoid Heat-Seeking Missile, the key was to notice the guiding crosshair when the missile was initially launched. By the time that was finished, the speed with which Heat-Seeking Missile fell from the sky was far faster than the speed of any character.

You could do your best to dodge it, but you would only be able to avoid the center of the blast, reducing only some of the damage that you took.

In this moment, what Samsara’s three players cared more about was: attack.

Their control of Dancing Rain would definitely be broken after this attack, and they would definitely suffer a heavy loss. So, right now, what they had to do above all else was to kill Dancing Rain.

Their formation, which from the start had been meant to suppress Dancing Rain, was still useful. Dancing Rain had no extra space to dodge the attacks that the three launched against her.

The audience couldn’t see what was going on in the mushroom cloud. All they could see was flickering silhouettes and the flashes of skills being used. Samsara’s three players couldn’t worry about controlling the situation right now. They each used their most powerful attacks. And then, the audience watched as the four players’ health bars plummeted.

Whose health would reach the bottom first? Whose health would remain above zero?

Everyone’s hearts were in their throats as they stared at those four health bars. Whether the broadcast or the live displays, all screens were currently showing a close-up of their health bars.

Zero!

Of the four health bars, one reached zero first.

Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves?

This was everyone’s instinctive answer. After all, he had the least health out of them all, only 11%. He shouldn’t be able to tank a Heat-Seeking Missile.

But, no!

The name written above the health bar was Dancing Rain. Samsara’s focus fire as the missile had exploded had actually killed off Dancing Rain first.

The health bars of Cloud Piercer and One Autumn Leaf were still falling. Originally, they’d had around 30% remaining, so the damage of the Heat-Seeking Missile wouldn’t be enough to directly kill them. What about Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves?

Empty Waves’ health had actually been the first to stop falling. 0.7%, 0.7% remaining!

Empty Waves was still alive. In other words, this situation right now, Ye Xiu was facing a 1v3?

Happy lost.

Countless people were already thinking this. Even though Ye Xiu had faced a 1v3 in last round’s team battle, what he had done back then was simply self-preservation. Ye Xiu had only been able to control Samsara’s three players there because they had believed “3v1 is no problem for us, we can definitely take care of this very quickly.” He hadn’t truly restricted all three of them, let alone defeated the three of them.

And now, he needed to defeat three people in an upfront battle. How was that possible? This was what everyone was thinking. The audience couldn’t help but feel regret, seeing how Happy had worked so hard to get all the way here, only to face such a hopeless and helpless conclusion.

And for Samsara, this was truly fortunate.

Such an unforeseen wave of attack had actually ended with them having the upper hand.

The Best Partners had been disintegrated. Happy had only Ye Xiu remaining, while Samsara had their three strongest remaining.

We won!

At this moment, they could have this thought, right?

Jiang Botao, whose character had only 0.7% remaining, felt this fortune most clearly. He had just barely managed to escape the clutches of death. Empty Waves was still alive thanks to the small adjustments he’d made as Lord Grim had approached. At that time, he had felt an instinct of self-preservation. There was no fear in closing in on Dancing Rain, but when Lord Grim arrived, he of course felt that it was more appropriate to retreat, put some distance between them. Moreover, the Heat-Seeking Missile that Su Mucheng fired of course wouldn’t center upon Empty Waves, who was already at low health. Thus, in the end, Empty Waves was the Samsara character closest to the edge of the blast radius. Added to his high defense from plate armor and his subconscious evasive maneuvers when the missile came down, Empty Waves had taken the least amount of damage.

How wonderful it is to live! Victory is best enjoyed when alive!

These were Jiang Botao’s honest thoughts at this moment. But, they were only thoughts. He didn’t even have the chance to feel any emotions before Empty Waves’ health suddenly dropped again.

Zero!

Empty Waves died.

Jiang Botao was stunned. He was completely sure that the damage from the Heat-Seeking Missile had already stopped. This was damage that a new skill had instantly created, not prolonged damage from an old attack.

What was this?

His camera view floated upward. Upon the grayed-out screen, Jiang Botao saw a shuriken piercing the chest of Empty Waves’ fallen form.

Finishing blow…

The Heat-Seeking Missile didn’t kill him, but Ye Xiu’s follow-up attack did.

This attack had come so fast that there’d been less than one second’s difference between it and the damage of Heat-Seeking Missile. Never mind the fact that Jiang Botao hadn’t noticed it – even if he had, he had no way of dodging such a fast and accurate finishing blow.

They hadn’t won yet.

They hadn’t finished yet.

Heat-Seeking Missile was only the beginning. From the very start, Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng had realized that in that kind of situation, even if Dancing Rain let loose that strike, there was no way she could escape that encirclement. She would definitely be focused by Samsara and killed.

But Ye Xiu had already prepared the finishing blow.

0.7%, Empty Waves avoided death by only 0.7%. Such a small difference meant that even Jiang Botao didn’t dare confirm in that moment that Empty Waves would live. But Ye Xiu accurately predicted, and his final hit had come so accurately, so flawlessly.

Be careful!

It’s not over yet!

Now was the time for Ye Xiu to deal the finishing blow!

Jiang Botao desperately wanted to send this information to his two remaining teammates. He knew that because Heat-Seeking Missile dealt immense damage, and because they’d been focused on nothing but killing Dancing Rain, the Samsara players had had no chance to do anything besides a few subconscious evasive maneuvers. Right now, they were still suffering the aftershocks of the explosion. And Ye Xiu was planning to use this moment to instantaneously kill all three of them.

1v3 was an impossible task, but under these special conditions, Jiang Botao felt danger. Because he sensed that deep trust between Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng, as well as all sorts of confidence. Ye Xiu trusted that Su Mucheng could absolutely pull off a map explosion, and Su Mucheng firmly believed that, after Dancing Rain fell, Ye Xiu would be able to execute the finishing blows alone.

Glory isn’t a single-player game. This was the view that Ye Xiu had always maintained. Even now, when he was the only one left on the battlefield, the plan that he carried out still embodied this belief. In this final scene that everyone had worked so hard to set up, he brought everyone’s hard work to the ultimate conclusion.

“Watch out!!” But Jiang Botao could not make his voice heard. The light from the explosion had yet to fade, but with his camera view floating upward, he saw a silhouette darting forward like a bolt of lightning, overlapping with another silhouette.

Even under the cover of the light and smoke, Jiang Botao could recognize that second silhouette. It was one with which he was incomparably familiar, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer.

Powerful Knee Strike!

Aerial Twist!

Two skills in a row, both from the weapon of a Fighter class.

When the Powerful Knee Strike came close, Zhou Zekai detected it. He swiftly adjusted the position of Cloud Piercer’s body, which had been thrown into the air from the force of the blast, in order to fire at the approaching Lord Grim. But by the time the gunfire sounded, Lord Grim’s two legs were already locked around his neck.

Twist!

Lord Grim twisted his body in midair, and the bullets fired by Cloud Piercer slammed against the ground. Ye Xiu didn’t wait for this skill to land before cancelling it. While still spinning, he was already unsheathing his sword – Collapsing Mountain.

Without anything to push off against in midair, the Collapsing Mountain naturally didn’t have any leaping effect. It was simply an attack that swept straight downward, cleaving Cloud Piercer.

The two silhouettes crashed downward, but then Lord Grim’s skill changed again, the blade that swung down suddenly swept upward again, Upwards Slash!

Cloud Piercer was going up and down as though he were riding a roller coaster. Because of how rapidly and relentlessly Lord Grim was switching skills and attack directions, Zhou Zekai’s figure was never moving in the same direction, not even for a moment. Under this kind of rhythm, even Zhou Zekai had absolutely no way to adjust.

How fast did he have to be?

In the eyes of ordinary gamers, this was simply unimaginable, this was breaking the game’s design. In their eyes, in this short amount of time, a skill couldn’t even be completed, right?

But the pro players knew, Ye Xiu was able to execute these skills so quickly because, over the course of this process, he was forcibly canceling skills nonstop. Every skill used the shortest and most direct path to hit the opponent, and then, without even waiting for the skill to finish dealing all of its damage, he was immediately canceling it, and then using the next skill, repeating the process. Used in this way, these skills weren’t dealing all of the damage that they could, but the changes were fast to the extreme. And such fast changes meant that Zhou Zekai had no way to counter.

This was the theory behind this. But how accurate of a judgment was needed for this? How fast of a hand speed?

Use a skill, cancel it, and on top of all this, Lord Grim still had to worry about changing weapon forms as well.

What kind of hand speed?

The pro players were stunned. They had all experienced the unspecialized blitz, but this was their first time witnessing it this fast, this densely packed. Calling this God-level was frankly an insult. This was beyond God-level!

Falling Flower Palm, Anti-Tank Missile, Gatling Gun.

In the blink of an eye, three more skills. Just as closely packed, just as fast. The moment that Falling Flower Palm came out, those who weren’t pro players practically didn’t see it at all. And then, Cloud Piercer was already being swallowed in the explosion of the Anti-Tank Missiles, and by then, the high-speed bullets of Gatling Gun were already sinking into his flesh. Along with the blowback from Falling Flower Palm, they sent Cloud Piercer flying.

Zero!

Cloud Piercer’s health hit zero!

Zhou Zekai had had no chance at all to adjust. Because the skills were packed together so densely, Cloud Piercer was rapidly spinning and flying in every which direction. He had absolutely no way to adjust.

Died!

Cloud Piercer died.

3.5 seconds ago, Ye Xiu faced a 1v3.

3 seconds ago, Ye Xiu faced a 1v2.

And now, 1v1.

Jiang Botao, Zhou Zekai.

The captain and vice captain who had led Samsara to two championships, Ye Xiu had killed both of them in the span of 3.5 seconds. Even if the two characters had already been at critical health, even if the two of them had suffered a huge impact from the Heat-Seeking Missile – killing them in 3.5 seconds, this was enough to be called a miracle.

There were no words to describe it. The stadium was filled with clamoring shouts. Because the changes were too fast, everyone had seen different things at every moment. While one person was still shouting because of something he’d caught, another person had noticed something something else.

But no matter what, Empty Waves, Cloud Piercer, these two characters had truly fallen, fallen without a single chance to fight back. And then, One Autumn Leaf, this character that Ye Xiu had built by his own hand, was the final target that he had to kill.

Chapter 1725 - They Are the Champions

3.5 seconds.

Sun Xiang had experienced countless 3.5 seconds over the course of his professional career. But in the future, even many years after his retirement, these 3.5 seconds of the Glory Professional Alliance Season 10 finals would be forever engraved in his memory.

Amidst the explosion of the Heat-Seeking Missile, the three Samsara players had killed Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain. Even Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves, who’d only had 11% health at the time, had fortunately managed to survive.

3v1.

Champions!

What a logical train of thought. Sun Xiang didn’t feel that it was wrong for him to have this kind of thought at this moment. He didn’t feel that he had relaxed his guard or anything. His controls remained as attentive as ever as he adjusted One Autumn Leaf, stabilizing him after the blast of the explosion.

And then, he watched as Empty Waves’ sliver of health was suddenly wiped clean.

And then, he watched as Lord Grim rushed toward Cloud Piercer, fighting so rapidly that Cloud Piercer was rendered helpless.

3.5 seconds.

At the time, Sun Xiang didn’t have an accurate sense of the time that had elapsed. Everything that happened had caught him completely off-guard. His awareness couldn’t keep up with Lord Grim’s attack movements at all. He was hurriedly stabilizing One Autumn Leaf, but as he prepared to rush through the dissipating smoke and fire to help his teammate, Cloud Piercer was already sent crashing toward him.

Corpse.

Glory’s number one player Zhou Zekai, the Great Gunner Cloud Piercer. In 3.5 seconds, he’d become a corpse flying in his direction.

In interviews many years later, Sun Xiang would be utterly unable to use words to describe his emotions in that moment. But he knew very clearly: those 3.5 seconds were not, in fact, the most frightening moment of his professional career.

What frightened him the most, what made him feel true fear, were not those 3.5 seconds, but the 3 seconds that came after.

One Autumn Leaf dodged Cloud Piercer’s corpse. Sun Xiang hadn’t even completely awoken from his shock when Lord Grim, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, had already rushed up to him.

Awareness?

Sun Xiang clearly remembered, in that moment, he had no awareness. All of his controls were conditioned reflexes, subconscious reactions.

These kind of reactions and controls, done without thought, should be the fastest. But Sun Xiang would also remember clearly, in that moment, he was slow, too slow. Compared to Ye Xiu’s controls, compared to Lord Grim’s movements, everything that he did was far too slow.

Overlapping Sidesteps?

Probably! Sun Xiang had no way of confirming. All he saw were afterimages. While his brain was still trying to analyze Lord Grim’s movements, Lord Grim was already beginning his next skill.

Dragon Tooth?

He was Bleeding? This was an effect that could only come from a Double Stab. Had there been a Double Stab after the Dragon Tooth?

Moonlight Slash?

Two injuries? Had it already become Full Moonlight Slash?

The attacks just came so fast, the skills just changed so fast, he couldn’t keep up with the rhythm, there was no time to react. Sun Xiang never would have expected, in this kind of confrontation of pure skill and technique, that he could be so helpless, that he could be so thoroughly overwhelmed.

3 seconds.

He seemed to have made many controls himself, but not a single one had been effective. He could only watch as One Autumn Leaf’s health slid downward. The blast of the Heat-Seeking Missile had already taken most of his health from him, and in an instant, it reached the end.

3 seconds.

Sun Xiang only understood one thing.

He now knew how Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer had been killed…

Starfall!

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella fell like a meteor. This Exorcist skill was the final attack that Lord Grim used, the attack that ended it all. Without wavering, without hesitation, the meteor-like Myriad Manifestations Umbrella pierced One Autumn Leaf’s chest. This character that Ye Xiu had built himself, this character that had been honored as the Battle God, fell.

GLORY!

The word flashed on the screen.

The exact same word and font as the in-game Arena. But at this moment, this word was a symbol of the very highest glory.

Championship.

Glory Season 10, Glory’s champions, Team Happy!

It was over. Everything had come to an end.

In the broadcast, commentator Pan Lin was shouting this result with all his might, and Li Yibo, who had experienced another face-slapping for his analysis, was also feeling his heart swell with emotion.

Restraint, he needed restraint! Li Yibo reminded himself over and over, he had to maintain his image of calm rationality. But Pan Lin, who was roaring next to him as though he were a diehard Happy fan, was about to grab him in a hug. Faced with this devotion, this passion, Li Yibo finally could hold himself back no longer. He suddenly remembered Glory Season 4, the scene when their Tyranny had defeated Excellent Era. At the time, hadn’t they been just like Happy today, challenging and defeating the all-powerful kings?

“Damn, fucking incredible!” Li Yibo was finally shouting as well. Bearing? Rationality? How could any of that compare to the thrill of victory?

A 6.5 second victory. 6.5 seconds decided the championship. This was absolutely unprecedented in Glory history.

We won!

We won!!!

The moment the word flashed onscreen, everyone in Happy’s player area leapt to their feet. Chen Guo instantly started crying, her tears flying onto those next to her.

No one mocked her for it. How could Chen Guo be the only one who felt like crying right now?

Wei Chen looked like he didn’t know what to do with his hands and feet. It seemed as though he wanted to ignore the ban on smoking in the stadium to light a cigarette, but the match he lit ended up almost burning his own hair. They did it, they’d actually done it. After so many years, returning to the Pro Alliance as the oldest player, he’d actually managed to get a championship?

“This guy!!” The cigarette that had never even been lit in the first place was fiercely ground out by Wei Chen.

“Fuck!” Fang Rui cursed, because Wei Chen had ground that cigarette on his thigh. But aside from this curse, he couldn’t care about it any more. In fact, whether this shout was cursing Wei Chen or expressing his emotions, even Fang Rui didn’t know. Championship, he had won the championship! Transferring as an All-Star to the grassroots Team Happy, class changing from the number one Thief to a Qi Master, Fang Rui had done so many things that most people wouldn’t even dare thinking about. But, he had succeeded. He had won the championship that every pro player dreamed of.

“Beautifully done!” Fang Rui praised fiercely. It was praise for himself, as well as praise for his teammates. And at the same time, he remembered his former partner, who had bid farewell to the professional stage after the second round of the playoffs, Lin Jingyan.

Do you see this, Old Lin? Me, the champion!

“Amazing, we’re champions, amazing…” Luo Ji was also extremely moved. Even though he may not have contributed very much, he, as a part of Team Happy as a whole, shared everyone’s feelings clearly. He very much wanted to find someone to share his excitement with, but his closer friends Qiao Yifan and An Wenyi were still in their player booths, while Wei Chen and Fang Rui were two seniors. Who else? Luo Ji looked at Mo Fan, and had a fright.

Mo Fan’s facial expression was contorting. That face of his never seemed to be able to display a moved or excited expression, and right now, it looked as though he didn’t even know what muscles to use to show these emotions. The expression that resulted was as broken as it could be.

Luo Ji laughed. Laughter or tears, everyone had their own ways of expressing their excitement!

“We won,” Luo Ji said to Mo Fan.

He didn’t get an answer. Mo Fan simply looked at him, and nodded once with all his strength.

We won! We really won the championship!

In the away team audience section, with the guild members led by Wu Chen at the center, everyone was uncontrollably cheering and screaming and jumping. Their excitement, their emotion, it was indescribable. But compared to the stadium as a whole, this area of excitement felt a bit abrupt.

For the Samsara fans, this was a moment of disappointment. A few still gave their applause to the victors, but most of them were silently tasting the bitterness of defeat.

Just a little more, and they could be celebrating like those fans in the away team section right now. But, 6.5 seconds, everything had changed in 6.5 seconds. The last one standing on the battlefield had been Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim; the final victor was Happy.

“These guys, they actually did it…”

There were surprised exclamations, there were emotional sighs.

No one dreamed of the championship as much as the pro players did. And among them, only a small portion would ever be able to achieve this honor. Any championship winner was worthy of their admiration, of their respect.

Happy, a new team.

Ye Xiu, an old player that many people had viewed as outdated.

In Season 10, they stood tall upon the summit of Glory.

They were the champions!

(nom it will make me very happy if you put this in, please) T/N: “With this battle, we will make everyone remember the moment we were crowned with Glory.” — “Light from Dust”, TKA live action opening theme.

Chapter 1726 - Fortunate to Meet You

Happy, an unbelievable team.

Glory Season 10, an unbelievable championship.

The pro players all rose to their feet and delivered their heartfelt applause.

At this time, there was nothing but congratulations. Continuing discussion about technique at this time would interfere with the atmosphere. Still, Ye Xiu’s final 6.5 seconds of consecutive finishing blows was just too earth-shattering – everyone was visibly moved. Yet the stadium did not report the statistics of that final moment. Even the stadium’s large display screen didn’t show many replays of this incredible, iconic moment.

This was, after all, Samsara’s home stadium. They had to look after their self-interests, which meant caring about the mood of the home team. In a short while, they would be conducting the award ceremony for Team Happy, which was annoying enough. There was no need to rub salt in the wound! This final moment would be remembered, but in this stadium right now, most people did not want to see it.

The statistics were not shown in the live stadium, but the televised broadcast did not have such concerns. Those 6.5 seconds were on repeat, as though this scene could never be watched enough times. And the data of these 6.5 seconds were already calculated.

What everyone was most anxious to know was, of course, Ye Xiu’s hand speed during those 6.5 seconds.

How fast had his controls needed to be, in order to display such changing, densely-packed attacks?

APM, 764!

This was the final conclusion displayed by the system. Although it wasn’t shown in the live stadium, the pro players all received the report through various means.

“Is he even human?”

This group of people, already considered inhuman to most ordinary gamers, began frenzied complaints of “this guy just isn’t human” about Ye Xiu.

Compared to how shocked everyone else was, those from Heavenly Swords had been a bit more mentally prepared. Especially Sun Zheping, because he had fought alongside Happy and Ye Xiu before. Having interacted with the unspecialized Lord Grim more often, he had a better understanding of this character. Added to his thorough experience, after seeing Ye Xiu’s moves during those 6.5 seconds, he already had a rough estimate as to what Ye Xiu’s hand speed must have been. The final statistic confirmed his judgment.

Even so, that didn’t mean he wasn’t shocked. More than that, though, he felt admiration.

764 APM, this was a first even in Ye Xiu’s professional career. Even if no class beside the unspecialized allowed room for performing this many inputs in a row, everyone knew that Ye Xiu had truly surpassed the limit. This was an explosion that could not be replicated. An old player who was already at the end of his professional career, what kind of determination and willpower had he needed to manifest this transcendence?

Ye Xiu…

He was the unquestionable star of this moment. The stadium was already making preparations for the award ceremony. Everyone was staring at Ye Xiu’s competitor booth, waiting to see him emerge and walk onto the award stage.

The uproar in the stadium was sealed off by the soundproof walls of the competitor booth. After he took off his headphones, the entire world was quiet.

Victory. At last, victory.

After many years, he finally tasted the championship once again. He felt relaxed, he felt joyful, and most importantly, he felt satisfied.

Yes. Nothing satisfied Ye Xiu more than victory, more than the championship.

Right now, he sat upon his chair, and he savored this complete peace, savored this greatest satisfaction.

He subconsciously reached for a cigarette, but after feeling his pocket, he remembered where he was.

Things were no longer as they once were. How could he smoke in today’s competitor booths? The automatic fire extinguishers would put it out immediately.

It’d been too long since he’d won the championship. He couldn’t keep up with the times!

Ye Xiu laughed at himself. Seven years, after seven years. The Glory Alliance of seven years ago lagged far behind what it was today, and the rules were still being perfected step by step. Back then, as the saying went, one cigarette after a match, become a living immortal. Especially that cigarette after winning a championship. That was truly the most perfect way of winding down.

But now…

Oh well. Head out first!

Ye Xiu stood up, and finally walked out of the competitor booth.

Lights!

Countless spotlights had been waiting for this moment. The moment that Ye Xiu appeared outside of his competitor booth, they all focused upon him, shining upon his body. The stadium was filled with cheers, shouts, applause, for although this was their away game, Happy’s fans carried enough passion and enthusiasm. When Ye Xiu walked out of the booth, all of this reached a peak. The stadium shone its lights, Happy’s fans cheered for him, Samsara’s fans delivered their applause as well.

“Boss!” Steamed Bun sprinted over. Happy’s other players had already walked out of their competitor booths, and those who had been sitting in the player area were already onstage as well.

Championship. A feeling that he hadn’t experienced in a long time.

But this scene was something that Ye Xiu had never experienced before. He had unparalleled competition experience; he’d won the greatest number of championships in the entire Alliance. But never before had he celebrated alongside his teammates directly after a match, never before had he directly accepted the award. In Excellent Era’s time, he had stay mysterious and lie low. He had always quietly arrived, quietly competed, and quietly left.

Ten years, his fourth championship. Yet this was the first time Ye Xiu stood directly under the eyes of millions of people and accepted all of the glory and blessings.

Happy’s members high-fived and hugged each other. Some were crying, some laughing, but at this moment, no matter how much someone might lose their composure, they would be forgiven. Nothing was too embarrassing.

To the side, Samsara’s players quietly finished lining up. Happy’s joy was their pain. But they still stood there, neither leaving the stage nor interrupting Happy’s celebration. They had lost this match, lost this entire season, lost the Samsara dynasty that they had almost established, but they did not lose their bearing.

“Congratulations.” In the end, as the losers, they shook hands with Happy, gave them their well-wishes, and then left. They were the hosts of this place, but they were not the stars of this moment.

After Samsara left, the preparations for the award ceremony were complete, with an award stage set up right in the center of the stadium floor. One by one, Happy’s players walked onto the stage.

The chairman of the Alliance, Feng Xianjun, was led onstage, his face shining with joy.

“Incredible, truly incredible.” Feng Xianjun gave all of the Happy players such praise as he presented a championship ring, the symbol of the championship, to each person.

“What weak vocab!” Ye Xiu mercilessly pointed this out when it was his turn.

Feng Xianjun gave Ye Xiu a strong pat on the back. He may not have used any fancy vocabulary, but the word came from his genuine feelings. Feng Xianjun felt that this word was was the best summary of Team Happy and each of its players.

“You are the most incredible!” he said to Ye Xiu, and he gave him the championship ring that belonged to him, his fourth one.

Ten players, ten championship rings.

And then, the championship trophy was finally delivered onstage as well. It represented the whole, belonging to the whole team, and just now, under the engraving of “Season 10,” the team name “Happy” had been added.

Offstage, the tears that Chen Guo had only just managed to stop began to flow again.

She wasn’t a player, so of course she wouldn’t stand upon the award stage. But she didn’t feel any regret because of this. She already felt that she was a winner in life, from head to toe.

Right now, she wasn’t thinking about blueprints for the future of their now-championship team. All of her thoughts were of the past, the past that belonged to Happy.

That snowy night, the ordinary guy who walked into Happy Internet Café.

That guy who had used her Chasing Haze to defeat, in 40 seconds, the opponent who had beaten her for 52 rounds straight, and then lamented that he had been slow because his hands were cold.

That guy who had seemed a bit serious as he told her, “Actually, I’m Ye Qiu.”

That guy.

From a new server in the Glory game, using a completely new character, he restarted his Glory journey.

Snatching dungeon records, dealing with all of the major guilds trying to kill them, building Guild Happy, pioneering, spying, stealing Wild Bosses, competing in events; and then applying for the Challenger League, overcoming all of the difficulties along the way, defeating Excellent Era in the finals to enter the Alliance, arriving at the pro battles, fighting from the regular season to the playoffs, never meeting defeat in an individual battle, and finally, in 6.5 seconds, killing Samsara’s most powerful trio, leading Happy to stand upon the summit of Glory.

These two-plus years, growing from nothing, drop by drop. Although Chen Guo hadn’t personally experienced much of it, it was still vivid before her eyes. She knew better than anyone the hard work that Ye Xiu had put in; she understood better than anyone the sacrifices Ye Xiu had made.

And now, everything that he had done had paid off.

Championship. This was the best reward, one that he fully deserved.

As for Chen Guo, she felt that she was very fortunate.

Fortunate that, on that snowy night, Ye Xiu had walked into her Internet café.

Fortunate that, on that snowy night, she had taken in Ye Xiu.

Happy’s everything had begun on that day.

On that day, I was fortunate to meet you, the most incredible you.

Chapter 1727 - The Strongest Opponent, The Greatest Friend

“The Season 10 Championship goes to… Team Happy!!”

Amidst thunderous applause, the championship trophy, representing the whole, belonging to their team, engraved with “Season 10, Team Happy,” was awarded to Team Happy by Alliance Chairman Feng Xianjun. The person to represent Happy and take it from the chairman’s hands was naturally their captain, Ye Xiu!

This was his fourth championship trophy, yet this was the first time he had ever personally received the trophy directly from the Alliance. Everyone’s gazes were fixed upon this scene, bearing witness to this fourth, and also first, champion’s crowning.

The trophy.

The gleaming golden trophy, symbolizing the greatest Glory, was finally given to Happy.

Ye Xiu accepted it with both hands. But immediately afterwards, the trophy slipped between his fingers.

“Ah!!”

As the crowd cried out in surprise, to Ye Xiu’s left and right, Su Mucheng and Fang Rui swiftly reached out to support the trophy. Then, hand after hand reached over, holding the trophy steady. Happy was no longer standing in a line on the stage, but gathered around Ye Xiu in a circle.

“Hey, even if you already have plenty of these, don’t throw this one away! I haven’t had one yet!” Fang Rui informed him in a serious tone.

“Exactly!” The others all agreed.

Ye Xiu smiled.

Obviously, he wasn’t trying to throw the trophy away. But his hands were exhausted, and he just didn’t have the strength to hold up the trophy.

Luckily, he had so many reliable teammates standing beside him.

They might’ve noticed this early on, which was why they all reached out their hands. Together, they helped Ye Xiu raise the trophy above their heads.

We are the champions!

In this moment, even though they weren’t the home team of this stadium, they received plenty of applause. After the official award ceremony was over, Chen Guo also walked onto the stage, gathering with the rest of Happy, either crying or laughing; it wasn’t important.

This moment belonged to Happy, but since it wasn’t their home stadium, they had to limit their celebrations. After the award ceremony, Happy soon retreated backstage.

Even if it was the deciding match of the grand finals, the post-match press conference still had to go on.

Samsara soon arrived for their interview. There were simply too many spectacular moments to this battle, but from Zhou Zekai’s opening 1v3 in the group arena to Tang Rou’s counter 1v3 to the amazing performance from each and every player in the team competition, none of it could outshine the radiance of Ye Xiu’s 6.5 second triple kill.

That was an extremely difficult finishing blow, the deciding finishing blow. Naturally, when discussing their thoughts on the match, Samsara’s players couldn’t avoid being asked about their thoughts on Ye Xiu’s performance.

“He’s an extraordinary player.” This was what Samsara’s Captain Zhou Zekai said. Words were not his strong point, but he crowned Ye Xiu with an adjective like “extraordinary,” to which the other members of Samsara all expressed their agreement. They had lost, but they accepted it. Ye Xiu, and Team Happy as a whole, had achieved too many miraculous things. Their efforts and their accomplishments were all worthy of respect.

“We look forward to the next time we face them!” This hope of Samsara’s could be considered the highest level of acknowledgement to an opponent.

After Samsara, the stars of the night took the floor. The reporters had all prepared their questions. But as it turned out, Happy’s lineup for this press conference did not include Ye Xiu.

Everyone was stunned, and after congratulating Happy on their win, everyone’s first question became: “Why isn’t Ye Xiu here to attend the press conference?”

“He’s exhausted. He needs rest.” This was Su Mucheng’s reply to the reporters’ question. It didn’t matter if everyone believed it or not, because either way, they couldn’t do anything about it. But a Team Happy press conference without Ye Xiu was one missing its protagonist, missing its skeleton; it had suddenly become uninteresting.

In the later press releases regarding Happy’s championships, there was a distinct lack of interviews with Ye Xiu. There wasn’t even a single sentence from the man. Even Chang Xian, the Esports Home reporter that had always been close with Happy, had his requests for an interview rejected by Team Happy.

The star of the championship, refusing all interviews? The new reporters to the Glory circle all felt that this was unbelievable. However, the veteran reporters who had ten years of experience interviewing the Glory circle all felt a sense of nostalgia.

No reports on the star of the championship, wasn’t this the very scene of that three year Excellent Era dynasty? Never mind an interview, the Ye Xiu of that era didn’t even reveal his face once.

Was this guy returning to the past?

For a while, everyone was coming up with theories, and none of them gave up on getting that interview from Ye Xiu. However, no one had expected that the image of him raising the Glory Season 10 championship trophy with his Happy teammates would be the final impression that Ye Xiu left upon Glory.

On the fourth day after the finals had ended, Team Happy held a press conference. Originally, everyone had thought that Ye Xiu was finally here to take interviews, but to everyone’s surprise, only Team Happy’s boss Chen Guo and Su Mucheng attended. And then, during the press conference, they announced Ye Xiu’s retirement.

Retirement?

Ye Xiu was retiring?

True, it had already happened once, and Ye Xiu’s age was clear to see. But the undefeated streak he had left in the individual match record, and the 6.5 second triple kill that overwhelmed Samsara’s three top players, had caused everyone to forget these facts. Everyone believed, with Ye Xiu’s current state, Ye Xiu’s current skill level, he could fight on for another ten years, no problem!

But, retirement?

Such a sudden and resolute decision, and he hadn’t even personally come out to notify everyone. He was leaving just like that?

Why?

Everyone wanted to know the reason, but Happy’s boss Chen Guo didn’t seem willing to discuss it. Her smile seemed rather forced as well. Clearly, she was the most reluctant to see Ye Xiu leave. She would love nothing more than for Ye Xiu to stay.

However….

“It’s time to go home.” That was the reason Ye Xiu had given them, when he made the decision. He didn’t hide his reluctance to leave Glory, or set down his passion for the championship. He just let everyone knew that he had another duty.

“You’ll always be welcome if you decide to return.” Chen Guo didn’t want Ye Xiu to leave, but she couldn’t stop him from leaving. She just hoped, anticipated, that perhaps Ye Xiu might get approval from his family, that perhaps he might not have to ever make such sacrifices again, but be able to uphold both at the same time.

She hoped so.

Chen Guo silently looked forward to such a moment. She never stopped hoping.

“He’s going home,” was what she told the reporters. This was the reason for Ye Xiu’s retirement, as well as his direction after his departure. This answer had the reporters confused, but Chen Guo didn’t explain further.

“As for Team Happy, Su Mucheng will take up the position of captain.” Chen Guo accepted Ye Xiu’s decision. She didn’t fall because of his choice, and she wouldn’t let Happy fall, either. As for Su Mucheng, after Ye Xiu made his decision, she didn’t act in a way that made people worry. She knew this was Ye Xiu’s personal decision, a mature decision. She wouldn’t let herself become a reason for Ye Xiu to worry. She would only continue to support Ye Xiu to the best of her ability, and sweep away the worries that he couldn’t let go of.

Thus, she would no longer only play that small role. She was going to take on all that Ye Xiu had done and become Team Happy’s core in the days to come, just like Ye Xiu, all the way until she retired.

“Keep in touch, I’ll wait for you to retire.” This was the promise she and Ye Xiu made when they parted.

News of Ye Xiu’s retirement spread like wildfire, sending waves through the entire Glory scene. Like last time, he left without a single word, and then everyone found out about his retirement through the news.

Disappointment, sadness, well-wishes, confusion…

All sorts of emotions and responses. Two and a half years ago, everyone had already experienced this once. However, this time, their emotions were much more complicated, because in these two and a half years, from the game servers to the Challenger League to the Pro League, this guy had made his existence very well known, sweeping through like a tornado, turning the world upside down.

But in the end, once again silently and suddenly, he left just like that?

Was he planning on hiding in a corner and then suddenly stabbing everyone when they weren’t looking?

Some people’s joking theories immediately earned widespread acknowledgement. Yet after tossing around a discussion of Ye Xiu’s shamelessness, everyone fell into silence again.

In the end, the only thing everyone offered up were well-wishes.

To their strongest opponent.

To their greatest friend..